{"nodes":[{"pos":[244,409],"content":"Represents the method that will handle the <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.IO.FileSystemWatcher.Error\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> event of a <bpt id=\"p2\">&lt;xref href=\"System.IO.FileSystemWatcher\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p2\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> object.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"Represents the method that will handle the <xref href=\"System.IO.FileSystemWatcher.Error\"></xref> event of a <xref href=\"System.IO.FileSystemWatcher\"></xref> object."},{"pos":[421,821],"content":"When you create an ErrorEventHandler delegate, you identify the method that will handle the event. To associate the event with your event-handling method, add an instance of the delegate to the event. The event-handling method is called whenever the event occurs, unless you remove the delegate. For more information about event-handler delegates, see [Events](~/add/includes/ajax-current-ext-md.md).","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"extradata":"MT","nodes":[{"content":"When you create an ErrorEventHandler delegate, you identify the method that will handle the event.","pos":[0,98]},{"content":"To associate the event with your event-handling method, add an instance of the delegate to the event.","pos":[99,200]},{"content":"The event-handling method is called whenever the event occurs, unless you remove the delegate.","pos":[201,295]},{"content":"For more information about event-handler delegates, see <bpt id=\"p1\">[</bpt>Events<ept id=\"p1\">](~/add/includes/ajax-current-ext-md.md)</ept>.","pos":[296,400],"source":" For more information about event-handler delegates, see [Events](~/add/includes/ajax-current-ext-md.md)."}]}],"content":"### YamlMime:ManagedReference\nitems:\n- uid: System.IO.ErrorEventHandler\n  id: ErrorEventHandler\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: ErrorEventHandler\n  nameWithType: ErrorEventHandler\n  fullName: System.IO.ErrorEventHandler\n  type: Delegate\n  summary: Represents the method that will handle the <xref href=\"System.IO.FileSystemWatcher.Error\"></xref> event of a <xref href=\"System.IO.FileSystemWatcher\"></xref> object.\n  remarks: When you create an ErrorEventHandler delegate, you identify the method that will handle the event. To associate the event with your event-handling method, add an instance of the delegate to the event. The event-handling method is called whenever the event occurs, unless you remove the delegate. For more information about event-handler delegates, see [Events](~/add/includes/ajax-current-ext-md.md).\n  example:\n  - \"The following code example shows how to create a `FileSystemWatcher` object to monitor file changes (creates, deletes, renames, changes) occurring on a disk drive. The example also shows how to properly receive error notifications.  \\n  \\n [!code-cs[FileSystemWatcher#1](~/add/codesnippet/csharp/t-system.io.erroreventha_1.cs)]\\n [!code-vb[FileSystemWatcher#1](~/add/codesnippet/visualbasic/t-system.io.erroreventha_1.vb)]\"\n  syntax:\n    content: public delegate void ErrorEventHandler(object sender, ErrorEventArgs e);\n  inheritance:\n  - System.Delegate\n  platform:\n  - net462\nreferences:\n- uid: System.Delegate\n  isExternal: false\n  name: System.Delegate\n"}