{"nodes":[{"pos":[303,421],"content":"Represents the method that will handle the event raised by an exception that is not handled by the application domain.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Represents the method that will handle the event raised by an exception that is not handled by the application domain.","pos":[0,118]}]},{"pos":[434,1104],"content":"An UnhandledExceptionEventHandler can only be specified for the default application domain that is created by the system to execute an application. Specifying an UnhandledExceptionEventHandler for an <xref:System.AppDomain> created by an application has no effect.       When you create an UnhandledExceptionEventHandler delegate, you identify the method that will handle the event. To associate the event handler with your event, add an instance of the delegate to the event. The event handler is called whenever the event occurs, unless you remove the delegate. For more information about event handler delegates, see [Events](~/add/includes/ajax-current-ext-md.md).","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"extradata":"MT","nodes":[{"content":"An UnhandledExceptionEventHandler can only be specified for the default application domain that is created by the system to execute an application.","pos":[0,147]},{"content":"Specifying an UnhandledExceptionEventHandler for an &lt;xref:System.AppDomain&gt; created by an application has no effect.","pos":[148,264],"source":" Specifying an UnhandledExceptionEventHandler for an <xref:System.AppDomain> created by an application has no effect."},{"content":"When you create an UnhandledExceptionEventHandler delegate, you identify the method that will handle the event.","pos":[271,382]},{"content":"To associate the event handler with your event, add an instance of the delegate to the event.","pos":[383,476]},{"content":"The event handler is called whenever the event occurs, unless you remove the delegate.","pos":[477,563]},{"content":"For more information about event handler delegates, see <bpt id=\"p1\">[</bpt>Events<ept id=\"p1\">](~/add/includes/ajax-current-ext-md.md)</ept>.","pos":[564,668],"source":" For more information about event handler delegates, see [Events](~/add/includes/ajax-current-ext-md.md)."}]}],"content":"### YamlMime:ManagedReference\nitems:\n- uid: System.UnhandledExceptionEventHandler\n  id: UnhandledExceptionEventHandler\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: UnhandledExceptionEventHandler\n  nameWithType: UnhandledExceptionEventHandler\n  fullName: System.UnhandledExceptionEventHandler\n  type: Delegate\n  summary: Represents the method that will handle the event raised by an exception that is not handled by the application domain.\n  remarks: \"An UnhandledExceptionEventHandler can only be specified for the default application domain that is created by the system to execute an application. Specifying an UnhandledExceptionEventHandler for an <xref:System.AppDomain> created by an application has no effect.  \\n  \\n When you create an UnhandledExceptionEventHandler delegate, you identify the method that will handle the event. To associate the event handler with your event, add an instance of the delegate to the event. The event handler is called whenever the event occurs, unless you remove the delegate. For more information about event handler delegates, see [Events](~/add/includes/ajax-current-ext-md.md).\"\n  syntax:\n    content: >-\n      [System.Runtime.InteropServices.ComVisible(true)]\n\n      public delegate void UnhandledExceptionEventHandler(object sender, UnhandledExceptionEventArgs e);\n  inheritance:\n  - System.Delegate\n  platform:\n  - net462\nreferences:\n- uid: System.Delegate\n  isExternal: false\n  name: System.Delegate\n"}