{"nodes":[{"pos":[246,395],"content":"Represents the method that handles asynchronous events such as application events. This delegate is called at the start of an asynchronous operation.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Represents the method that handles asynchronous events such as application events. This delegate is called at the start of an asynchronous operation.","pos":[0,149],"nodes":[{"content":"Represents the method that handles asynchronous events such as application events.","pos":[0,82]},{"content":"This delegate is called at the start of an asynchronous operation.","pos":[83,149]}]}]},{"pos":[408,841],"content":"When you create a BeginEventHandler delegate, you identify the method that will handle the event. To associate the event with your event handler, add an instance of the delegate to the event. The event handler is called whenever the event occurs, unless you remove the delegate. For more information about event-handler delegates, see [NIB: Events and Delegates](http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/d98fd58b-fa4f-4598-8378-addf4355a115).","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"extradata":"MT","nodes":[{"content":"When you create a BeginEventHandler delegate, you identify the method that will handle the event.","pos":[0,97]},{"content":"To associate the event with your event handler, add an instance of the delegate to the event.","pos":[98,191]},{"content":"The event handler is called whenever the event occurs, unless you remove the delegate.","pos":[192,278]},{"content":"For more information about event-handler delegates, see <bpt id=\"p1\">[</bpt>NIB: Events and Delegates<ept id=\"p1\">](http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/d98fd58b-fa4f-4598-8378-addf4355a115)</ept>.","pos":[279,433],"source":" For more information about event-handler delegates, see [NIB: Events and Delegates](http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/d98fd58b-fa4f-4598-8378-addf4355a115)."}]}],"content":"### YamlMime:ManagedReference\nitems:\n- uid: System.Web.BeginEventHandler\n  id: BeginEventHandler\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: BeginEventHandler\n  nameWithType: BeginEventHandler\n  fullName: System.Web.BeginEventHandler\n  type: Delegate\n  summary: Represents the method that handles asynchronous events such as application events. This delegate is called at the start of an asynchronous operation.\n  remarks: 'When you create a BeginEventHandler delegate, you identify the method that will handle the event. To associate the event with your event handler, add an instance of the delegate to the event. The event handler is called whenever the event occurs, unless you remove the delegate. For more information about event-handler delegates, see [NIB: Events and Delegates](http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/d98fd58b-fa4f-4598-8378-addf4355a115).'\n  example:\n  - \"The following code example uses the BeginEventHandler delegate to register a handler an asynchronous page.  \\n  \\n> [!IMPORTANT]\\n>  This example has a text box that accepts user input, which is a potential security threat. By default, ASP.NET Web pages validate that user input does not include script or HTML elements. For more information, see [Script Exploits Overview](~/add/includes/ajax-current-ext-md.md).  \\n  \\n [!code-vb[PageAddOnPreRenderCompleteAsync#1](~/add/codesnippet/visualbasic/t-system.web.begineventh_1.aspx)]\\n [!code-cs[PageAddOnPreRenderCompleteAsync#1](~/add/codesnippet/csharp/t-system.web.begineventh_1.aspx)]\"\n  syntax:\n    content: public delegate IAsyncResult BeginEventHandler(object sender, EventArgs e, AsyncCallback cb, object extraData);\n  inheritance:\n  - System.Delegate\n  platform:\n  - net462\nreferences:\n- uid: System.Delegate\n  isExternal: false\n  name: System.Delegate\n"}