{"nodes":[{"pos":[305,402],"content":"Represents the method that will handle the requests of execution of some code in another context.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Represents the method that will handle the requests of execution of some code in another context.","pos":[0,97]}]},{"pos":[414,761],"content":"Callbacks provide a facility to request execution of some code in another context. The CrossContextDelegate class is defined for context callbacks. Each context has a callback object that can be used to perform callbacks on the context. The delegate used to request a callback through the callback object must be of the CrossContextDelegate class.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Callbacks provide a facility to request execution of some code in another context. The CrossContextDelegate class is defined for context callbacks. Each context has a callback object that can be used to perform callbacks on the context. The delegate used to request a callback through the callback object must be of the CrossContextDelegate class.","pos":[0,347],"nodes":[{"content":"Callbacks provide a facility to request execution of some code in another context.","pos":[0,82]},{"content":"The CrossContextDelegate class is defined for context callbacks.","pos":[83,147]},{"content":"Each context has a callback object that can be used to perform callbacks on the context.","pos":[148,236]},{"content":"The delegate used to request a callback through the callback object must be of the CrossContextDelegate class.","pos":[237,347]}]}]}],"content":"### YamlMime:ManagedReference\nitems:\n- uid: System.Runtime.Remoting.Contexts.CrossContextDelegate\n  id: CrossContextDelegate\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: CrossContextDelegate\n  nameWithType: CrossContextDelegate\n  fullName: System.Runtime.Remoting.Contexts.CrossContextDelegate\n  type: Delegate\n  summary: Represents the method that will handle the requests of execution of some code in another context.\n  remarks: Callbacks provide a facility to request execution of some code in another context. The CrossContextDelegate class is defined for context callbacks. Each context has a callback object that can be used to perform callbacks on the context. The delegate used to request a callback through the callback object must be of the CrossContextDelegate class.\n  syntax:\n    content: >-\n      [System.Runtime.InteropServices.ComVisible(true)]\n\n      public delegate void CrossContextDelegate();\n  inheritance:\n  - System.Delegate\n  platform:\n  - net462\nreferences:\n- uid: System.Delegate\n  isExternal: false\n  name: System.Delegate\n"}