{"nodes":[{"pos":[969,1279],"content":"Serves as the base class for controls that reside in <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> zones, and that provide catalogs of available Web server controls (especially <bpt id=\"p2\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p2\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> controls) that users can add to a Web page.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"Serves as the base class for controls that reside in <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"></xref> zones, and that provide catalogs of available Web server controls (especially <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"></xref> controls) that users can add to a Web page."},{"pos":[1292,5605],"content":"The CatalogPart class is a base class for special controls that reside in <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> zones. These derived CatalogPart controls provide catalogs of Web server controls that end users can add to a Web page. Use CatalogPart controls in a Web application when you want to provide end users with the flexibility to change the functionality of a Web page by adding or removing server controls.       A catalog is simply a list of one or more available Web server controls (including <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls, ASP.NET server controls, and custom or user controls) that users can add to a Web page. A catalog has a number of common characteristics, including instruction text for end users; text to describe each server control; helper controls to select the server controls and add them to the page; a common header, footer, and border; and a number of style attributes.       There are three types of CatalogPart controls provided with the Web Parts control set, as described in the following table. Each type of CatalogPart control contains server controls that are added to a page from a different source.      > [!IMPORTANT] >  Controls that inherit from the CatalogPart class can reside only in zones derived from the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> class.      |Control|Description|   |-------------|-----------------|   |<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PageCatalogPart>|Contains controls that have been closed on a page, and that can be reopened (added back to the page) by users. The controls in this type of catalog are controls that were already added to the page from another source, and were then closed by a user.|   |<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart>|Contains server controls declared within a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart> control, which is itself contained in a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> zone in the markup of a Web page.|   |<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>|Provides the user interface (UI) for a user to upload a control's definition file (an XML file defined by a schema, that contains state information) to a catalog, so that the control can be added to a Web page. The controls themselves do not appear in this type of catalog; the catalog is just a mechanism for accessing the definition files for external controls so they can be added to a page.|       The CatalogPart class inherits from the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part> class, so that it has the common behavior of other part controls in the Web Parts control set. In addition, it adds some members that are useful for the catalog functionality. The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.DisplayTitle%2A> property gets the actual string that is currently being displayed as the title of the control. The value of this property can be the same as the value of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> property or, if no value has been assigned to that property, a default value supplied by the .NET Framework. The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.WebPartManager%2A> and <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.Zone%2A> properties both provide convenient access to the two essential objects that control the life cycle of a CatalogPart control: the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager> control, and the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> zone that contains the CatalogPart control, respectively.       The CatalogPart class also contains several methods. The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method is declared as an abstract method that must be implemented by inheritors. Its intended purpose is to return a collection of descriptions of the controls in the catalog. A related method, <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A>, is also declared as abstract and must be implemented by inheritors. This method is intended to return an instance of a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control based on a description that is passed to the method as a parameter.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The CatalogPart class is a base class for special controls that reside in &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase&gt; zones.","pos":[0,138],"source":"The CatalogPart class is a base class for special controls that reside in <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> zones."},{"content":"These derived CatalogPart controls provide catalogs of Web server controls that end users can add to a Web page.","pos":[139,251]},{"content":"Use CatalogPart controls in a Web application when you want to provide end users with the flexibility to change the functionality of a Web page by adding or removing server controls.","pos":[252,434]},{"content":"A catalog is simply a list of one or more available Web server controls (including &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart&gt; controls, ASP.NET server controls, and custom or user controls) that users can add to a Web page.","pos":[441,671],"source":"       A catalog is simply a list of one or more available Web server controls (including <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls, ASP.NET server controls, and custom or user controls) that users can add to a Web page."},{"content":"A catalog has a number of common characteristics, including instruction text for end users; text to describe each server control; helper controls to select the server controls and add them to the page; a common header, footer, and border; and a number of style attributes.","pos":[672,944]},{"content":"There are three types of CatalogPart controls provided with the Web Parts control set, as described in the following table.","pos":[951,1074]},{"content":"Each type of CatalogPart control contains server controls that are added to a page from a different source.","pos":[1075,1182]},{"content":"&gt; <ph id=\"ph1\">[!IMPORTANT]</ph> &gt;  Controls that inherit from the CatalogPart class can reside only in zones derived from the &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase&gt; class.","pos":[1188,1361],"source":"      > [!IMPORTANT] >  Controls that inherit from the CatalogPart class can reside only in zones derived from the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> class."},{"content":"|Control|Description|   |-------------|-----------------|   |&lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PageCatalogPart&gt;|Contains controls that have been closed on a page, and that can be reopened (added back to the page) by users.","pos":[1367,1596],"source":"      |Control|Description|   |-------------|-----------------|   |<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PageCatalogPart>|Contains controls that have been closed on a page, and that can be reopened (added back to the page) by users."},{"content":"The controls in this type of catalog are controls that were already added to the page from another source, and were then closed by a user.|   |&lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart&gt;|Contains server controls declared within a &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart&gt; control, which is itself contained in a &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase&gt; zone in the markup of a Web page.|   |&lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart&gt;|Provides the user interface (UI) for a user to upload a control's definition file (an XML file defined by a schema, that contains state information) to a catalog, so that the control can be added to a Web page.","pos":[1597,2319],"source":" The controls in this type of catalog are controls that were already added to the page from another source, and were then closed by a user.|   |<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart>|Contains server controls declared within a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart> control, which is itself contained in a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> zone in the markup of a Web page.|   |<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>|Provides the user interface (UI) for a user to upload a control's definition file (an XML file defined by a schema, that contains state information) to a catalog, so that the control can be added to a Web page."},{"content":"The controls themselves do not appear in this type of catalog; the catalog is just a mechanism for accessing the definition files for external controls so they can be added to a page.|       The CatalogPart class inherits from the base &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part&gt; class, so that it has the common behavior of other part controls in the Web Parts control set.","pos":[2320,2697],"source":" The controls themselves do not appear in this type of catalog; the catalog is just a mechanism for accessing the definition files for external controls so they can be added to a page.|       The CatalogPart class inherits from the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part> class, so that it has the common behavior of other part controls in the Web Parts control set."},{"content":"In addition, it adds some members that are useful for the catalog functionality.","pos":[2698,2778]},{"content":"The &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.DisplayTitle%2A&gt; property gets the actual string that is currently being displayed as the title of the control.","pos":[2779,2947],"source":" The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.DisplayTitle%2A> property gets the actual string that is currently being displayed as the title of the control."},{"content":"The value of this property can be the same as the value of the &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A&gt; property or, if no value has been assigned to that property, a default value supplied by the .NET Framework.","pos":[2948,3175],"source":" The value of this property can be the same as the value of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> property or, if no value has been assigned to that property, a default value supplied by the .NET Framework."},{"content":"The &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.WebPartManager%2A&gt; and &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.Zone%2A&gt; properties both provide convenient access to the two essential objects that control the life cycle of a CatalogPart control: the &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager&gt; control, and the &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase&gt; zone that contains the CatalogPart control, respectively.","pos":[3176,3636],"source":" The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.WebPartManager%2A> and <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.Zone%2A> properties both provide convenient access to the two essential objects that control the life cycle of a CatalogPart control: the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager> control, and the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> zone that contains the CatalogPart control, respectively."},{"content":"The CatalogPart class also contains several methods.","pos":[3643,3695]},{"content":"The &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A&gt; method is declared as an abstract method that must be implemented by inheritors.","pos":[3696,3869],"source":" The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method is declared as an abstract method that must be implemented by inheritors."},{"content":"Its intended purpose is to return a collection of descriptions of the controls in the catalog.","pos":[3870,3964]},{"content":"A related method, &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A&gt;, is also declared as abstract and must be implemented by inheritors.","pos":[3965,4119],"source":" A related method, <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A>, is also declared as abstract and must be implemented by inheritors."},{"content":"This method is intended to return an instance of a &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart&gt; control based on a description that is passed to the method as a parameter.","pos":[4120,4296],"source":" This method is intended to return an instance of a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control based on a description that is passed to the method as a parameter."}]},{"pos":[20900,21020],"content":"Initializes the class for use by an inherited class instance. This constructor can only be called by an inherited class.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Initializes the class for use by an inherited class instance. This constructor can only be called by an inherited class.","pos":[0,120],"nodes":[{"content":"Initializes the class for use by an inherited class instance.","pos":[0,61]},{"content":"This constructor can only be called by an inherited class.","pos":[62,120]}]}]},{"pos":[21597,21731],"content":"Gets a string that contains the actual current title of a <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> control.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"Gets a string that contains the actual current title of a <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"></xref> control."},{"pos":[21744,22319],"content":"The DisplayTitle property returns either the current value of the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> property or, if the control has no title, a calculated value.       The DisplayTitle property is designed to be a read-only, calculated property to get the actual current value of the displayed title at run time. Therefore, you should not attempt to use this property to set a title for a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control. To set a title, use the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> property.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The DisplayTitle property returns either the current value of the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> property or, if the control has no title, a calculated value.       The DisplayTitle property is designed to be a read-only, calculated property to get the actual current value of the displayed title at run time. Therefore, you should not attempt to use this property to set a title for a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control. To set a title, use the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> property.","pos":[0,573],"nodes":[{"content":"The DisplayTitle property returns either the current value of the base &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A&gt; property or, if the control has no title, a calculated value.","pos":[0,188],"source":"The DisplayTitle property returns either the current value of the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> property or, if the control has no title, a calculated value."},{"content":"The DisplayTitle property is designed to be a read-only, calculated property to get the actual current value of the displayed title at run time.","pos":[195,339]},{"content":"Therefore, you should not attempt to use this property to set a title for a &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart&gt; control.","pos":[340,478],"source":" Therefore, you should not attempt to use this property to set a title for a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control."},{"content":"To set a title, use the base &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A&gt; property.","pos":[479,573],"source":" To set a title, use the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> property."}]}]},{"pos":[22968,23079],"content":"A string that represents the complete, visible title of the control. The default value is an empty string (\"\").","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"A string that represents the complete, visible title of the control. The default value is an empty string (\"\").","pos":[0,111],"nodes":[{"content":"A string that represents the complete, visible title of the control.","pos":[0,68]},{"content":"The default value is an empty string (\"\").","pos":[69,111]}]}]},{"pos":[23694,23834],"content":"Returns a collection of descriptions of the available <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> controls in a catalog.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"Returns a collection of descriptions of the available <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"></xref> controls in a catalog."},{"pos":[23847,24906],"content":"The GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions method returns description information for each control in a catalog. A <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object is a lightweight object that contains essential information about a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control, including its ID, an object reference to the control, and the values of several important properties that are inherited from the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part> class, such as <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> and <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Description%2A>.       The GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions method improves performance. When a catalog is created, it needs some information about each control it contains, including a title, a description, an icon (if one exists), and an ID. Rather than having to create an instance of each control to get this information, a caller can use the GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions method, which returns only the description information about each control.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions method returns description information for each control in a catalog. A <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object is a lightweight object that contains essential information about a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control, including its ID, an object reference to the control, and the values of several important properties that are inherited from the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part> class, such as <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> and <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Description%2A>.       The GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions method improves performance. When a catalog is created, it needs some information about each control it contains, including a title, a description, an icon (if one exists), and an ID. Rather than having to create an instance of each control to get this information, a caller can use the GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions method, which returns only the description information about each control.","pos":[0,1057],"nodes":[{"content":"The GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions method returns description information for each control in a catalog.","pos":[0,105]},{"content":"A &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription&gt; object is a lightweight object that contains essential information about a &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart&gt; control, including its ID, an object reference to the control, and the values of several important properties that are inherited from the base &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part&gt; class, such as &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A&gt; and &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Description%2A&gt;.","pos":[106,621],"source":" A <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object is a lightweight object that contains essential information about a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control, including its ID, an object reference to the control, and the values of several important properties that are inherited from the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part> class, such as <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> and <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Description%2A>."},{"content":"The GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions method improves performance.","pos":[628,692]},{"content":"When a catalog is created, it needs some information about each control it contains, including a title, a description, an icon (if one exists), and an ID.","pos":[693,847]},{"content":"Rather than having to create an instance of each control to get this information, a caller can use the GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions method, which returns only the description information about each control.","pos":[848,1057]}]}]},{"pos":[25173,25381],"content":"A <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> that contains a <bpt id=\"p2\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p2\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> for each control in a catalog.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"A <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection\"></xref> that contains a <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription\"></xref> for each control in a catalog."},{"pos":[25950,26073],"content":"Retrieves the current state of a <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> control's parent zone.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"Retrieves the current state of a <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"></xref> control's parent zone."},{"pos":[26085,26304],"content":"The GetDesignModeState method returns information about the state of the zone that contains a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control. The state information is returned in the form of a dictionary.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The GetDesignModeState method returns information about the state of the zone that contains a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control. The state information is returned in the form of a dictionary.","pos":[0,219],"nodes":[{"content":"The GetDesignModeState method returns information about the state of the zone that contains a &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart&gt; control.","pos":[0,156],"source":"The GetDesignModeState method returns information about the state of the zone that contains a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control."},{"content":"The state information is returned in the form of a dictionary.","pos":[157,219]}]}]},{"pos":[26494,26743],"content":"An &lt;xref:System.Collections.IDictionary&gt; that contains the current state of the <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> zone that contains a <bpt id=\"p2\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p2\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> control.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"An <xref:System.Collections.IDictionary> that contains the current state of the <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"></xref> zone that contains a <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"></xref> control."},{"pos":[27423,27653],"content":"Retrieves from a catalog the <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> control that is referenced by the <bpt id=\"p2\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p2\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> object passed to the method.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"Retrieves from a catalog the <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"></xref> control that is referenced by the <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription\"></xref> object passed to the method."},{"pos":[27666,28481],"content":"The GetWebPart method returns a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control from a catalog. The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object that is passed to the method matches a specific <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control and enables that control to be returned by the method.       If a catalog contains a server control that does not derive from the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> class, such as an ASP.NET server control, a custom server control, or a user control, a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control must wrap the server control with a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.GenericWebPart> control, and return the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.GenericWebPart> control from this method.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The GetWebPart method returns a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control from a catalog. The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object that is passed to the method matches a specific <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control and enables that control to be returned by the method.       If a catalog contains a server control that does not derive from the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> class, such as an ASP.NET server control, a custom server control, or a user control, a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control must wrap the server control with a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.GenericWebPart> control, and return the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.GenericWebPart> control from this method.","pos":[0,813],"nodes":[{"content":"The GetWebPart method returns a &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart&gt; control from a catalog.","pos":[0,105],"source":"The GetWebPart method returns a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control from a catalog."},{"content":"The &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription&gt; object that is passed to the method matches a specific &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart&gt; control and enables that control to be returned by the method.","pos":[106,338],"source":" The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object that is passed to the method matches a specific <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control and enables that control to be returned by the method."},{"content":"If a catalog contains a server control that does not derive from the &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart&gt; class, such as an ASP.NET server control, a custom server control, or a user control, a &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart&gt; control must wrap the server control with a &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.GenericWebPart&gt; control, and return the &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.GenericWebPart&gt; control from this method.","pos":[345,813],"source":"       If a catalog contains a server control that does not derive from the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> class, such as an ASP.NET server control, a custom server control, or a user control, a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control must wrap the server control with a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.GenericWebPart> control, and return the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.GenericWebPart> control from this method."}]}]},{"pos":[28768,28949],"content":"A <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> that contains a reference to a specific <bpt id=\"p2\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p2\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept>.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"A <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription\"></xref> that contains a reference to a specific <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"></xref>."},{"pos":[29036,29177],"content":"A <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> that is referenced by the object in the <bpt id=\"p2\">&lt;code&gt;</bpt><ph id=\"ph1\">description</ph><ept id=\"p2\">&lt;/code&gt;</ept> parameter.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"A <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"></xref> that is referenced by the object in the <code>description</code> parameter."},{"pos":[29753,29823],"content":"Raises the <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.Control.PreRender\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> event.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"Raises the <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.Control.PreRender\"></xref> event."},{"pos":[29835,30067],"content":"The OnPreRender method calls the base <xref:System.Web.UI.Control.OnPreRender%2A?displayProperty=fullName> method, and ensures that an instance of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> class has been created.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The OnPreRender method calls the base &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.Control.OnPreRender%2A?displayProperty=fullName&gt; method, and ensures that an instance of the &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase&gt; class has been created.","pos":[0,232],"source":"The OnPreRender method calls the base <xref:System.Web.UI.Control.OnPreRender%2A?displayProperty=fullName> method, and ensures that an instance of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> class has been created."}]},{"pos":[30218,30274],"content":"An <xref:System.EventArgs> that contains the event data.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"An &lt;xref:System.EventArgs&gt; that contains the event data.","pos":[0,56],"source":"An <xref:System.EventArgs> that contains the event data."}]},{"pos":[30471,30705],"content":"The <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> that contains the <bpt id=\"p2\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p2\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> control is <bpt id=\"p3\">&lt;xref uid=\"langword_csharp_null\" name=\"null\" href=\"\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p3\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept>.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"The <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"></xref> that contains the <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"></xref> control is <xref uid=\"langword_csharp_null\" name=\"null\" href=\"\"></xref>."},{"pos":[31262,31298],"content":"Sets design-time data for a control.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Sets design-time data for a control.","pos":[0,36]}]},{"pos":[31497,31586],"content":"An <xref:System.Collections.IDictionary> containing the design-time data for the control.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"An &lt;xref:System.Collections.IDictionary&gt; containing the design-time data for the control.","pos":[0,89],"source":"An <xref:System.Collections.IDictionary> containing the design-time data for the control."}]},{"pos":[32118,32243],"content":"Gets a reference to the current instance of the <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> class.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"Gets a reference to the current instance of the <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager\"></xref> class."},{"pos":[32255,32464],"content":"The WebPartManager property provides a way for a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control to access the current <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager> object on the page.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The WebPartManager property provides a way for a &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart&gt; control to access the current &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager&gt; object on the page.","pos":[0,209],"source":"The WebPartManager property provides a way for a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control to access the current <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager> object on the page."}]},{"pos":[32665,32765],"content":"The <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> for the current Web page.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"The <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager\"></xref> for the current Web page."},{"pos":[33243,33436],"content":"Gets a reference to the <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> zone that contains a <bpt id=\"p2\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p2\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> control.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"Gets a reference to the <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"></xref> zone that contains a <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"></xref> control."},{"pos":[33448,33683],"content":"The Zone property enables a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control to get a reference to its zone. Although the property is read-only, the underlying properties of the zone itself can be changed programmatically.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The Zone property enables a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control to get a reference to its zone. Although the property is read-only, the underlying properties of the zone itself can be changed programmatically.","pos":[0,235],"nodes":[{"content":"The Zone property enables a &lt;xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart&gt; control to get a reference to its zone.","pos":[0,121],"source":"The Zone property enables a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control to get a reference to its zone."},{"content":"Although the property is read-only, the underlying properties of the zone itself can be changed programmatically.","pos":[122,235]}]}]},{"pos":[33876,34005],"content":"A <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> that corresponds to the zone that contains the control.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"A <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"></xref> that corresponds to the zone that contains the control."}],"content":"### YamlMime:ManagedReference\nitems:\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  id: CatalogPart\n  children:\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.#ctor\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.DisplayTitle\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetDesignModeState\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetWebPart(System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription)\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.OnPreRender(System.EventArgs)\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.SetDesignModeState(System.Collections.IDictionary)\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.WebPartManager\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.Zone\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: CatalogPart\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  type: Class\n  summary: Serves as the base class for controls that reside in <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"></xref> zones, and that provide catalogs of available Web server controls (especially <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"></xref> controls) that users can add to a Web page.\n  remarks: \"The CatalogPart class is a base class for special controls that reside in <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> zones. These derived CatalogPart controls provide catalogs of Web server controls that end users can add to a Web page. Use CatalogPart controls in a Web application when you want to provide end users with the flexibility to change the functionality of a Web page by adding or removing server controls.  \\n  \\n A catalog is simply a list of one or more available Web server controls (including <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls, ASP.NET server controls, and custom or user controls) that users can add to a Web page. A catalog has a number of common characteristics, including instruction text for end users; text to describe each server control; helper controls to select the server controls and add them to the page; a common header, footer, and border; and a number of style attributes.  \\n  \\n There are three types of CatalogPart controls provided with the Web Parts control set, as described in the following table. Each type of CatalogPart control contains server controls that are added to a page from a different source.  \\n  \\n> [!IMPORTANT]\\n>  Controls that inherit from the CatalogPart class can reside only in zones derived from the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> class.  \\n  \\n|Control|Description|  \\n|-------------|-----------------|  \\n|<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PageCatalogPart>|Contains controls that have been closed on a page, and that can be reopened (added back to the page) by users. The controls in this type of catalog are controls that were already added to the page from another source, and were then closed by a user.|  \\n|<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart>|Contains server controls declared within a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart> control, which is itself contained in a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> zone in the markup of a Web page.|  \\n|<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>|Provides the user interface (UI) for a user to upload a control's definition file (an XML file defined by a schema, that contains state information) to a catalog, so that the control can be added to a Web page. The controls themselves do not appear in this type of catalog; the catalog is just a mechanism for accessing the definition files for external controls so they can be added to a page.|  \\n  \\n The CatalogPart class inherits from the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part> class, so that it has the common behavior of other part controls in the Web Parts control set. In addition, it adds some members that are useful for the catalog functionality. The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.DisplayTitle%2A> property gets the actual string that is currently being displayed as the title of the control. The value of this property can be the same as the value of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> property or, if no value has been assigned to that property, a default value supplied by the .NET Framework. The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.WebPartManager%2A> and <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.Zone%2A> properties both provide convenient access to the two essential objects that control the life cycle of a CatalogPart control: the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager> control, and the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> zone that contains the CatalogPart control, respectively.  \\n  \\n The CatalogPart class also contains several methods. The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method is declared as an abstract method that must be implemented by inheritors. Its intended purpose is to return a collection of descriptions of the controls in the catalog. A related method, <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A>, is also declared as abstract and must be implemented by inheritors. This method is intended to return an instance of a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control based on a description that is passed to the method as a parameter.\"\n  example:\n  - \"The following code example demonstrates the use of the CatalogPart class. Because the class is abstract, it is not used directly in code. However, the example shows how to work with the three derived CatalogPart controls provided with the Web Parts control set to demonstrate common usage scenarios.  \\n  \\n There are four parts to the code example:  \\n  \\n-   A user control that enables you to change display modes on the Web page.  \\n  \\n-   A Web page, which contains the three CatalogPart controls provided with the Web Parts control set, all declared within a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> on a Web page. The page also contains a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartZone> control, with an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.AdRotator> control declared in the zone.  \\n  \\n-   An XML file that contains quotations displayed in the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.AdRotator> control on the Web page.  \\n  \\n-   An explanation of how to run the example.  \\n  \\n The first part of this code example is the user control that enables users to change display modes on a Web page. You should save this code in a file named DisplayModeMenuCS.ascx or DisplayModeMenuVB.ascx (depending on which language you are using). For details about display modes and a description of the source code in this control, see [Walkthrough: Changing Display Modes on a Web Parts Page](~/add/includes/ajax-current-ext-md.md).  \\n  \\n [!code-cs[WebParts_CatalogPart_Overview#5](~/add/codesnippet/csharp/t-system.web.ui.webcontr_53_1.ascx)]\\n [!code-vb[WebParts_CatalogPart_Overview#5](~/add/codesnippet/visualbasic/t-system.web.ui.webcontr_53_1.ascx)]  \\n  \\n The second part of the code example is the Web page. The page contains a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> control, and within the child `<zonetemplate>` element, each of the three CatalogPart controls provided with the Web Parts control set is declared. Some attribute are set on the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart> control, and also in the \\\\<script> section of the page, the attributes on that control are accessed programmatically. The control contains one child control that a user can add to the page:  a standard <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Calendar> control. The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> and CatalogPart control will only be visible when the user switches the page to catalog display mode.  \\n  \\n The page also contains a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartZone> control, and within its child `<zonetemplate>` element is an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.AdRotator> control that displays alternating messages from an XML file. If a user closes the control by clicking its close verb when the page is displayed, the control is added to the page catalog, and the user can reopen the control by switching the page into catalog display mode, accessing the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PageCatalogPart> control, and adding back the closed control.  \\n  \\n [!code-cs[WebParts_CatalogPart_Overview#1](~/add/codesnippet/csharp/t-system.web.ui.webcontr_53_2.aspx)]\\n [!code-vb[WebParts_CatalogPart_Overview#1](~/add/codesnippet/visualbasic/t-system.web.ui.webcontr_53_2.aspx)]  \\n  \\n The third part of the code example is the XML file. This file is a source file for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.AdRotator> control that is declared on the page. The file contains favorite quotations, which the control periodically rotates and displays. Copy the following content into a text editor, and save the file as Quotes.xml.  \\n  \\n```  \\n<?xml version=\\\"1.0\\\" encoding=\\\"utf-8\\\" ?>  \\n<Advertisements>  \\n  <Ad>  \\n    <AlternateText>  \\n      A stitch in time saves nine.  \\n    </AlternateText>      \\n  </Ad>  \\n  <Ad>  \\n    <AlternateText>  \\n      A penny saved is a penny earned.  \\n    </AlternateText>      \\n  </Ad>  \\n</Advertisements>  \\n```  \\n  \\n To run the code example, load the Web page in a browser. Use the **Display Modes** drop-down control to select **Catalog** and switch the page to catalog display mode. Notice the effects of the various property values that were set on the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart> control that contains the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Calendar> control. You can select the check box next to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Calendar> control, and click **Add** to add it to the page. If you click the **Display DeclarativeCatalogPart Properties** button, the values of the properties for that control are displayed. You can click **Close** to return the page to normal browse mode and see the added control on the page. Now go to the verbs menu on the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.AdRotator> control (represented by the downward arrow in the title bar) and click **Close**. The control is closed and added to the page catalog. Switch the page into catalog display mode again, and click the Page Catalog hyperlink to display the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PageCatalogPart> control. Note that the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.AdRotator> control is referenced there by its title, **Favorite Quotes**. Select the **Favorite Quotes** control, and click the **Add** button to add the control back to the page. Click the **Close** button to return the page to browse mode.  \\n  \\n> [!NOTE]\\n>  The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control is also declared on this page, but a sample showing how to import controls is more involved, so full use of the control is not demonstrated in this code example. To see a full working example, see the class overview documents for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class or the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> class.\"\n  syntax:\n    content: >-\n      [System.ComponentModel.Bindable(false)]\n\n      [System.ComponentModel.Designer(\"System.Web.UI.Design.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPartDesigner, System.Design, Version=4.0.0.0, Culture=neutral, PublicKeyToken=b03f5f7f11d50a3a\")]\n\n      public abstract class CatalogPart : System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part\n  inheritance:\n  - System.Object\n  - System.Web.UI.Control\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part\n  implements: []\n  inheritedMembers:\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.Adapter\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.AddedControl(System.Web.UI.Control,System.Int32)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.AddParsedSubObject(System.Object)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ApplyStyleSheetSkin(System.Web.UI.Page)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.AppRelativeTemplateSourceDirectory\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.BeginRenderTracing(System.IO.TextWriter,System.Object)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.BindingContainer\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.BuildProfileTree(System.String,System.Boolean)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ChildControlsCreated\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ClearCachedClientID\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ClearChildControlState\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ClearChildState\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ClearChildViewState\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ClearEffectiveClientIDMode\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ClientID\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ClientIDMode\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ClientIDSeparator\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.Context\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.CreateChildControls\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.CreateControlCollection\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.DataBind(System.Boolean)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.DataBindChildren\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.DataBinding\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.DataItemContainer\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.DataKeysContainer\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.DesignMode\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.Dispose\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.Disposed\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.EnableViewState\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.EndRenderTracing(System.IO.TextWriter,System.Object)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.EnsureChildControls\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.EnsureID\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.Events\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.FindControl(System.String)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.FindControl(System.String,System.Int32)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.Focus\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.GetRouteUrl(System.Object)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.GetRouteUrl(System.String,System.Object)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.GetRouteUrl(System.String,System.Web.Routing.RouteValueDictionary)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.GetRouteUrl(System.Web.Routing.RouteValueDictionary)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.GetUniqueIDRelativeTo(System.Web.UI.Control)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.HasChildViewState\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.HasControls\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.HasEvents\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ID\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.IdSeparator\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.Init\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.IsChildControlStateCleared\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.IsLiteralContent\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.IsTrackingViewState\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.IsViewStateEnabled\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.Load\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.LoadControlState(System.Object)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.LoadViewStateByID\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.MapPathSecure(System.String)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.NamingContainer\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.OnBubbleEvent(System.Object,System.EventArgs)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.OnDataBinding(System.EventArgs)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.OnInit(System.EventArgs)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.OnLoad(System.EventArgs)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.OnUnload(System.EventArgs)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.OpenFile(System.String)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.Page\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.Parent\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.PreRender\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.RaiseBubbleEvent(System.Object,System.EventArgs)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.RemovedControl(System.Web.UI.Control)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.RenderChildren(System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.RenderControl(System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.RenderControl(System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter,System.Web.UI.Adapters.ControlAdapter)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.RenderingCompatibility\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ResolveAdapter\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ResolveClientUrl(System.String)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ResolveUrl(System.String)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.SaveControlState\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.SetRenderMethodDelegate(System.Web.UI.RenderMethod)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.SetTraceData(System.Object,System.Object)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.SetTraceData(System.Object,System.Object,System.Object)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.Site\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.System#Web#UI#IControlBuilderAccessor#ControlBuilder\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.System#Web#UI#IControlDesignerAccessor#GetDesignModeState\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.System#Web#UI#IControlDesignerAccessor#SetDesignModeState(System.Collections.IDictionary)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.System#Web#UI#IControlDesignerAccessor#SetOwnerControl(System.Web.UI.Control)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.System#Web#UI#IControlDesignerAccessor#UserData\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.System#Web#UI#IDataBindingsAccessor#DataBindings\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.System#Web#UI#IDataBindingsAccessor#HasDataBindings\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.System#Web#UI#IExpressionsAccessor#Expressions\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.System#Web#UI#IExpressionsAccessor#HasExpressions\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.System#Web#UI#IParserAccessor#AddParsedSubObject(System.Object)\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.TemplateControl\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.TemplateSourceDirectory\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.UniqueID\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.Unload\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ValidateRequestMode\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ViewState\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ViewStateIgnoresCase\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.ViewStateMode\n  - System.Web.UI.Control.Visible\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel.AddAttributesToRender(System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter)\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel.BackImageUrl\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel.CreateControlStyle\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel.DefaultButton\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel.Direction\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel.GroupingText\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel.HorizontalAlign\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel.RenderBeginTag(System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter)\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel.RenderEndTag(System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter)\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel.ScrollBars\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel.SupportsDisabledAttribute\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel.Wrap\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.AccessKey\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.ApplyStyle(System.Web.UI.WebControls.Style)\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.Attributes\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.BackColor\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.BorderColor\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.BorderStyle\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.BorderWidth\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.ControlStyle\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.ControlStyleCreated\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.CopyBaseAttributes(System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl)\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.CssClass\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.DisabledCssClass\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.Enabled\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.EnableTheming\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.Font\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.ForeColor\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.HasAttributes\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.Height\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.IsEnabled\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.LoadViewState(System.Object)\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.MergeStyle(System.Web.UI.WebControls.Style)\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.Render(System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter)\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.RenderContents(System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter)\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.SaveViewState\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.SkinID\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.Style\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.System#Web#UI#IAttributeAccessor#GetAttribute(System.String)\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.System#Web#UI#IAttributeAccessor#SetAttribute(System.String,System.String)\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.TabIndex\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.TagKey\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.TagName\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.ToolTip\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.TrackViewState\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebControl.Width\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.ChromeState\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.ChromeType\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Controls\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.DataBind\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Description\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.System#Web#UI#WebControls#ICompositeControlDesignerAccessor#RecreateChildControls\n  - System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.#ctor\n  id: '#ctor'\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: CatalogPart()\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.CatalogPart()\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.CatalogPart()\n  type: Constructor\n  assemblies:\n  - System.Web\n  namespace: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts\n  summary: Initializes the class for use by an inherited class instance. This constructor can only be called by an inherited class.\n  syntax:\n    content: protected CatalogPart ();\n    parameters: []\n  overload: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.#ctor*\n  exceptions: []\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.DisplayTitle\n  id: DisplayTitle\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: DisplayTitle\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.DisplayTitle\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.DisplayTitle\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System.Web\n  namespace: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts\n  summary: Gets a string that contains the actual current title of a <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"></xref> control.\n  remarks: \"The DisplayTitle property returns either the current value of the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> property or, if the control has no title, a calculated value.  \\n  \\n The DisplayTitle property is designed to be a read-only, calculated property to get the actual current value of the displayed title at run time. Therefore, you should not attempt to use this property to set a title for a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control. To set a title, use the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> property.\"\n  example:\n  - \"The following code example demonstrates programmatic use of the DisplayTitle property. In the `<script>` section of the page, the code accesses the DisplayTitle property of `DeclarativeCatalogPart1` that is declared on the page. This code shows only the Web page; for the full code required to run the example, see the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> class overview.  \\n  \\n [!code-cs[XpsCreate#XpsCreateAddPkgContent](~/add/codesnippet/csharp/XpsCreate/XpsCreate.cs#xpscreateaddpkgcontent)]\"\n  syntax:\n    content: public string DisplayTitle { get; }\n    return:\n      type: System.String\n      description: A string that represents the complete, visible title of the control. The default value is an empty string (\"\").\n  overload: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.DisplayTitle*\n  exceptions: []\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions\n  id: GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions()\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions()\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions()\n  type: Method\n  assemblies:\n  - System.Web\n  namespace: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts\n  summary: Returns a collection of descriptions of the available <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"></xref> controls in a catalog.\n  remarks: \"The GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions method returns description information for each control in a catalog. A <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object is a lightweight object that contains essential information about a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control, including its ID, an object reference to the control, and the values of several important properties that are inherited from the base <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part> class, such as <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> and <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Description%2A>.  \\n  \\n The GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions method improves performance. When a catalog is created, it needs some information about each control it contains, including a title, a description, an icon (if one exists), and an ID. Rather than having to create an instance of each control to get this information, a caller can use the GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions method, which returns only the description information about each control.\"\n  syntax:\n    content: public abstract System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions ();\n    parameters: []\n    return:\n      type: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection\n      description: A <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection\"></xref> that contains a <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription\"></xref> for each control in a catalog.\n  overload: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions*\n  exceptions: []\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetDesignModeState\n  id: GetDesignModeState\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: GetDesignModeState()\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.GetDesignModeState()\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetDesignModeState()\n  type: Method\n  assemblies:\n  - System.Web\n  namespace: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts\n  summary: Retrieves the current state of a <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"></xref> control's parent zone.\n  remarks: The GetDesignModeState method returns information about the state of the zone that contains a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control. The state information is returned in the form of a dictionary.\n  syntax:\n    content: protected override System.Collections.IDictionary GetDesignModeState ();\n    parameters: []\n    return:\n      type: System.Collections.IDictionary\n      description: An <xref:System.Collections.IDictionary> that contains the current state of the <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"></xref> zone that contains a <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"></xref> control.\n  overload: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetDesignModeState*\n  exceptions: []\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetWebPart(System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription)\n  id: GetWebPart(System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription)\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: GetWebPart(WebPartDescription)\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.GetWebPart(WebPartDescription)\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetWebPart(WebPartDescription)\n  type: Method\n  assemblies:\n  - System.Web\n  namespace: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts\n  summary: Retrieves from a catalog the <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"></xref> control that is referenced by the <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription\"></xref> object passed to the method.\n  remarks: \"The GetWebPart method returns a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control from a catalog. The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object that is passed to the method matches a specific <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control and enables that control to be returned by the method.  \\n  \\n If a catalog contains a server control that does not derive from the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> class, such as an ASP.NET server control, a custom server control, or a user control, a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control must wrap the server control with a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.GenericWebPart> control, and return the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.GenericWebPart> control from this method.\"\n  syntax:\n    content: public abstract System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart GetWebPart (System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription description);\n    parameters:\n    - id: description\n      type: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription\n      description: A <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription\"></xref> that contains a reference to a specific <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"></xref>.\n    return:\n      type: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\n      description: A <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\"></xref> that is referenced by the object in the <code>description</code> parameter.\n  overload: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetWebPart*\n  exceptions: []\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.OnPreRender(System.EventArgs)\n  id: OnPreRender(System.EventArgs)\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: OnPreRender(EventArgs)\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.OnPreRender(EventArgs)\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.OnPreRender(EventArgs)\n  type: Method\n  assemblies:\n  - System.Web\n  namespace: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts\n  summary: Raises the <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.Control.PreRender\"></xref> event.\n  remarks: The OnPreRender method calls the base <xref:System.Web.UI.Control.OnPreRender%2A?displayProperty=fullName> method, and ensures that an instance of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> class has been created.\n  syntax:\n    content: protected override void OnPreRender (EventArgs e);\n    parameters:\n    - id: e\n      type: System.EventArgs\n      description: An <xref:System.EventArgs> that contains the event data.\n  overload: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.OnPreRender*\n  exceptions:\n  - type: System.InvalidOperationException\n    commentId: T:System.InvalidOperationException\n    description: The <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"></xref> that contains the <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"></xref> control is <xref uid=\"langword_csharp_null\" name=\"null\" href=\"\"></xref>.\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.SetDesignModeState(System.Collections.IDictionary)\n  id: SetDesignModeState(System.Collections.IDictionary)\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: SetDesignModeState(IDictionary)\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.SetDesignModeState(IDictionary)\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.SetDesignModeState(IDictionary)\n  type: Method\n  assemblies:\n  - System.Web\n  namespace: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts\n  summary: Sets design-time data for a control.\n  syntax:\n    content: protected override void SetDesignModeState (System.Collections.IDictionary data);\n    parameters:\n    - id: data\n      type: System.Collections.IDictionary\n      description: An <xref:System.Collections.IDictionary> containing the design-time data for the control.\n  overload: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.SetDesignModeState*\n  exceptions: []\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.WebPartManager\n  id: WebPartManager\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: WebPartManager\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.WebPartManager\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.WebPartManager\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System.Web\n  namespace: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts\n  summary: Gets a reference to the current instance of the <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager\"></xref> class.\n  remarks: The WebPartManager property provides a way for a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control to access the current <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager> object on the page.\n  syntax:\n    content: protected System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager WebPartManager { get; }\n    return:\n      type: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager\n      description: The <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager\"></xref> for the current Web page.\n  overload: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.WebPartManager*\n  exceptions: []\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.Zone\n  id: Zone\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: Zone\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.Zone\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.Zone\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System.Web\n  namespace: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts\n  summary: Gets a reference to the <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"></xref> zone that contains a <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\"></xref> control.\n  remarks: The Zone property enables a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> control to get a reference to its zone. Although the property is read-only, the underlying properties of the zone itself can be changed programmatically.\n  syntax:\n    content: protected System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase Zone { get; }\n    return:\n      type: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\n      description: A <xref href=\"System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\"></xref> that corresponds to the zone that contains the control.\n  overload: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.Zone*\n  exceptions: []\n  platform:\n  - net462\nreferences:\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part\n  isExternal: false\n  name: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part\n- uid: System.InvalidOperationException\n  isExternal: true\n  name: System.InvalidOperationException\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.#ctor\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: CatalogPart()\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.CatalogPart()\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.CatalogPart()\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.DisplayTitle\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: DisplayTitle\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.DisplayTitle\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.DisplayTitle\n- uid: System.String\n  parent: System\n  isExternal: true\n  name: String\n  nameWithType: String\n  fullName: System.String\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions()\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions()\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions()\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts\n  isExternal: false\n  name: WebPartDescriptionCollection\n  nameWithType: WebPartDescriptionCollection\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetDesignModeState\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: GetDesignModeState()\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.GetDesignModeState()\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetDesignModeState()\n- uid: System.Collections.IDictionary\n  parent: System.Collections\n  isExternal: true\n  name: IDictionary\n  nameWithType: IDictionary\n  fullName: System.Collections.IDictionary\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetWebPart(System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription)\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: GetWebPart(WebPartDescription)\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.GetWebPart(WebPartDescription)\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetWebPart(WebPartDescription)\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts\n  isExternal: false\n  name: WebPart\n  nameWithType: WebPart\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts\n  isExternal: false\n  name: WebPartDescription\n  nameWithType: WebPartDescription\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.OnPreRender(System.EventArgs)\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: OnPreRender(EventArgs)\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.OnPreRender(EventArgs)\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.OnPreRender(EventArgs)\n- uid: System.EventArgs\n  parent: System\n  isExternal: true\n  name: EventArgs\n  nameWithType: EventArgs\n  fullName: System.EventArgs\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.SetDesignModeState(System.Collections.IDictionary)\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: SetDesignModeState(IDictionary)\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.SetDesignModeState(IDictionary)\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.SetDesignModeState(IDictionary)\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.WebPartManager\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: WebPartManager\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.WebPartManager\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.WebPartManager\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts\n  isExternal: false\n  name: WebPartManager\n  nameWithType: WebPartManager\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.Zone\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: Zone\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.Zone\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.Zone\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts\n  isExternal: false\n  name: CatalogZoneBase\n  nameWithType: CatalogZoneBase\n  fullName: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.#ctor*\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: CatalogPart\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.CatalogPart\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.DisplayTitle*\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: DisplayTitle\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.DisplayTitle\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions*\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetDesignModeState*\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: GetDesignModeState\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.GetDesignModeState\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.GetWebPart*\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: GetWebPart\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.GetWebPart\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.OnPreRender*\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: OnPreRender\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.OnPreRender\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.SetDesignModeState*\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: SetDesignModeState\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.SetDesignModeState\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.WebPartManager*\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: WebPartManager\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.WebPartManager\n- uid: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart.Zone*\n  parent: System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart\n  isExternal: false\n  name: Zone\n  nameWithType: CatalogPart.Zone\n"}