{"nodes":[{"pos":[1033,1079],"content":"Represents an operating system process thread.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Represents an operating system process thread.","pos":[0,46]}]},{"pos":[1092,4102],"content":"Use ProcessThread to obtain information about a thread that is currently running on the system. Doing so allows you, for example, to monitor the thread's performance characteristics.      > [!IMPORTANT] >  This type implements the <xref:System.IDisposable> interface. When you have finished using the type, you should dispose of it either directly or indirectly. To dispose of the type directly, call its <xref:System.IDisposable.Dispose%2A> method in a `try`/`catch` block. To dispose of it indirectly, use a language construct such as `using` (in C#) or `Using` (in Visual Basic). For more information, see the “Using an Object that Implements IDisposable” section in the <xref:System.IDisposable> interface topic.       A thread is a path of execution through a program. It is the smallest unit of execution that Win32 schedules. It consists of a stack, the state of the CPU registers, and an entry in the execution list of the system scheduler.       A process consists of one or more threads and the code, data, and other resources of a program in memory. Typical program resources are open files, semaphores, and dynamically allocated memory. Each resource of a process is shared by all that process's threads.       A program executes when the system scheduler gives execution control to one of the program's threads. The scheduler determines which threads should run and when. A lower-priority thread might be forced to wait while higher-priority threads complete their tasks. On multiprocessor computers, the scheduler can move individual threads to different processors, thus balancing the CPU load.       Each process starts with a single thread, which is known as the primary thread. Any thread can create additional threads. All the threads within a process share the address space of that process.       The primary thread is not necessarily located at the first index in the collection.      > [!NOTE] >  Starting with the .NET Framework version 2.0, the ability to reference performance counter data on other computers has been eliminated for many of the .NET Framework methods and properties. This change was made to improve performance and to enable non-administrators to use the ProcessThread class. As a result, some applications that did not get exceptions in earlier versions of the .NET Framework may now get a <xref:System.NotSupportedException>. The methods and properties affected are too numerous to list here, but the exception information has been added to the affected member topics.       The threads of a process execute individually and are unaware of each other unless you make them visible to each other. Threads that share common resources, however, must coordinate their work by using semaphores or another method of interprocess communication.       To get a collection of all the ProcessThread objects associated with the current process, get the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.Threads%2A> property of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process> instance.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Use ProcessThread to obtain information about a thread that is currently running on the system.","pos":[0,95]},{"content":"Doing so allows you, for example, to monitor the thread's performance characteristics.","pos":[96,182]},{"content":"&gt; <ph id=\"ph1\">[!IMPORTANT]</ph> &gt;  This type implements the &lt;xref:System.IDisposable&gt; interface.","pos":[188,267],"source":"      > [!IMPORTANT] >  This type implements the <xref:System.IDisposable> interface."},{"content":"When you have finished using the type, you should dispose of it either directly or indirectly.","pos":[268,362]},{"content":"To dispose of the type directly, call its &lt;xref:System.IDisposable.Dispose%2A&gt; method in a <ph id=\"ph1\">`try`</ph><ph id=\"ph2\">/</ph><ph id=\"ph3\">`catch`</ph> block.","pos":[363,474],"source":" To dispose of the type directly, call its <xref:System.IDisposable.Dispose%2A> method in a `try`/`catch` block."},{"content":"To dispose of it indirectly, use a language construct such as <ph id=\"ph1\">`using`</ph> (in C#) or <ph id=\"ph2\">`Using`</ph> (in Visual Basic).","pos":[475,582],"source":" To dispose of it indirectly, use a language construct such as `using` (in C#) or `Using` (in Visual Basic)."},{"content":"For more information, see the “Using an Object that Implements IDisposable” section in the &lt;xref:System.IDisposable&gt; interface topic.","pos":[583,716],"source":" For more information, see the “Using an Object that Implements IDisposable” section in the <xref:System.IDisposable> interface topic."},{"content":"A thread is a path of execution through a program.","pos":[723,773]},{"content":"It is the smallest unit of execution that Win32 schedules.","pos":[774,832]},{"content":"It consists of a stack, the state of the CPU registers, and an entry in the execution list of the system scheduler.","pos":[833,948]},{"content":"A process consists of one or more threads and the code, data, and other resources of a program in memory.","pos":[955,1060]},{"content":"Typical program resources are open files, semaphores, and dynamically allocated memory.","pos":[1061,1148]},{"content":"Each resource of a process is shared by all that process's threads.","pos":[1149,1216]},{"content":"A program executes when the system scheduler gives execution control to one of the program's threads.","pos":[1223,1324]},{"content":"The scheduler determines which threads should run and when.","pos":[1325,1384]},{"content":"A lower-priority thread might be forced to wait while higher-priority threads complete their tasks.","pos":[1385,1484]},{"content":"On multiprocessor computers, the scheduler can move individual threads to different processors, thus balancing the CPU load.","pos":[1485,1609]},{"content":"Each process starts with a single thread, which is known as the primary thread.","pos":[1616,1695]},{"content":"Any thread can create additional threads.","pos":[1696,1737]},{"content":"All the threads within a process share the address space of that process.","pos":[1738,1811]},{"content":"The primary thread is not necessarily located at the first index in the collection.","pos":[1818,1901]},{"content":"&gt; <ph id=\"ph1\">[!NOTE]</ph> &gt;  Starting with the .NET Framework version 2.0, the ability to reference performance counter data on other computers has been eliminated for many of the .NET Framework methods and properties.","pos":[1907,2109],"source":"      > [!NOTE] >  Starting with the .NET Framework version 2.0, the ability to reference performance counter data on other computers has been eliminated for many of the .NET Framework methods and properties."},{"content":"This change was made to improve performance and to enable non-administrators to use the ProcessThread class.","pos":[2110,2218]},{"content":"As a result, some applications that did not get exceptions in earlier versions of the .NET Framework may now get a &lt;xref:System.NotSupportedException&gt;.","pos":[2219,2370],"source":" As a result, some applications that did not get exceptions in earlier versions of the .NET Framework may now get a <xref:System.NotSupportedException>."},{"content":"The methods and properties affected are too numerous to list here, but the exception information has been added to the affected member topics.","pos":[2371,2513]},{"content":"The threads of a process execute individually and are unaware of each other unless you make them visible to each other.","pos":[2520,2639]},{"content":"Threads that share common resources, however, must coordinate their work by using semaphores or another method of interprocess communication.","pos":[2640,2781]},{"content":"To get a collection of all the ProcessThread objects associated with the current process, get the &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.Threads%2A&gt; property of the &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.Process&gt; instance.","pos":[2788,2990],"source":"       To get a collection of all the ProcessThread objects associated with the current process, get the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.Threads%2A> property of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process> instance."}]},{"pos":[5576,5613],"content":"Gets the base priority of the thread.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Gets the base priority of the thread.","pos":[0,37]}]},{"pos":[5626,7253],"content":"The BasePriority is the starting priority for the process thread. You can view information about the base priority through the System Monitor's Priority Base counter.       The operating system computes a thread's base priority by combining the thread's priority level range with the process's priority class. You can set the process's <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityClass%2A?displayProperty=fullName> property to one of the values in the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass> enumeration, which are <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, or <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>. You can set the thread's <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityLevel%2A> property to a range of values that bounds the thread's base priority. Win32 uses four priority classes with seven base priority levels per class.       The thread's current priority might deviate from the base priority. For example, the operating system can change the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.CurrentPriority%2A> property based on the time elapsed or other boosts when a process must be put ahead of others for access to the processor. In addition, you can set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityBoostEnabled%2A> property to cause the system to temporarily boost the priority of a thread whenever the process is taken out of the wait state. The priority is reset when the process returns to the wait state.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The BasePriority is the starting priority for the process thread. You can view information about the base priority through the System Monitor's Priority Base counter.       The operating system computes a thread's base priority by combining the thread's priority level range with the process's priority class. You can set the process's <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityClass%2A?displayProperty=fullName> property to one of the values in the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass> enumeration, which are <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, or <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>. You can set the thread's <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityLevel%2A> property to a range of values that bounds the thread's base priority. Win32 uses four priority classes with seven base priority levels per class.       The thread's current priority might deviate from the base priority. For example, the operating system can change the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.CurrentPriority%2A> property based on the time elapsed or other boosts when a process must be put ahead of others for access to the processor. In addition, you can set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityBoostEnabled%2A> property to cause the system to temporarily boost the priority of a thread whenever the process is taken out of the wait state. The priority is reset when the process returns to the wait state.","pos":[0,1623],"nodes":[{"content":"The BasePriority is the starting priority for the process thread.","pos":[0,65]},{"content":"You can view information about the base priority through the System Monitor's Priority Base counter.","pos":[66,166]},{"content":"The operating system computes a thread's base priority by combining the thread's priority level range with the process's priority class.","pos":[173,309]},{"content":"You can set the process's &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityClass%2A?displayProperty=fullName&gt; property to one of the values in the &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass&gt; enumeration, which are &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass&gt;, &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass&gt;, &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass&gt;, &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass&gt;, &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass&gt;, or &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass&gt;.","pos":[310,809],"source":" You can set the process's <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityClass%2A?displayProperty=fullName> property to one of the values in the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass> enumeration, which are <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, or <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>."},{"content":"You can set the thread's &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityLevel%2A&gt; property to a range of values that bounds the thread's base priority.","pos":[810,961],"source":" You can set the thread's <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityLevel%2A> property to a range of values that bounds the thread's base priority."},{"content":"Win32 uses four priority classes with seven base priority levels per class.","pos":[962,1037]},{"content":"The thread's current priority might deviate from the base priority.","pos":[1044,1111]},{"content":"For example, the operating system can change the &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.CurrentPriority%2A&gt; property based on the time elapsed or other boosts when a process must be put ahead of others for access to the processor.","pos":[1112,1342],"source":" For example, the operating system can change the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.CurrentPriority%2A> property based on the time elapsed or other boosts when a process must be put ahead of others for access to the processor."},{"content":"In addition, you can set the &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityBoostEnabled%2A&gt; property to cause the system to temporarily boost the priority of a thread whenever the process is taken out of the wait state.","pos":[1343,1557],"source":" In addition, you can set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityBoostEnabled%2A> property to cause the system to temporarily boost the priority of a thread whenever the process is taken out of the wait state."},{"content":"The priority is reset when the process returns to the wait state.","pos":[1558,1623]}]}]},{"pos":[7367,7525],"content":"The base priority of the thread, which the operating system computes by combining the process priority class with the priority level of the associated thread.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The base priority of the thread, which the operating system computes by combining the process priority class with the priority level of the associated thread.","pos":[0,158]}]},{"pos":[7982,8022],"content":"Gets the current priority of the thread.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Gets the current priority of the thread.","pos":[0,40]}]},{"pos":[8034,8572],"content":"The thread's current priority might deviate from the base priority. For example, the operating system can change the CurrentPriority property based on the time elapsed, or other boosts, when a process must be put ahead of others for access to the processor. In addition, you can set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityBoostEnabled%2A> property to cause the system to temporarily boost the priority of a thread whenever the process is taken out of the wait state. The priority is reset when the process returns to the wait state.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The thread's current priority might deviate from the base priority. For example, the operating system can change the CurrentPriority property based on the time elapsed, or other boosts, when a process must be put ahead of others for access to the processor. In addition, you can set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityBoostEnabled%2A> property to cause the system to temporarily boost the priority of a thread whenever the process is taken out of the wait state. The priority is reset when the process returns to the wait state.","pos":[0,538],"nodes":[{"content":"The thread's current priority might deviate from the base priority.","pos":[0,67]},{"content":"For example, the operating system can change the CurrentPriority property based on the time elapsed, or other boosts, when a process must be put ahead of others for access to the processor.","pos":[68,257]},{"content":"In addition, you can set the &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityBoostEnabled%2A&gt; property to cause the system to temporarily boost the priority of a thread whenever the process is taken out of the wait state.","pos":[258,472],"source":" In addition, you can set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityBoostEnabled%2A> property to cause the system to temporarily boost the priority of a thread whenever the process is taken out of the wait state."},{"content":"The priority is reset when the process returns to the wait state.","pos":[473,538]}]}]},{"pos":[8688,8886],"content":"The current priority of the thread, which may deviate from the base priority based on how the operating system is scheduling the thread. The priority may be temporarily boosted for an active thread.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The current priority of the thread, which may deviate from the base priority based on how the operating system is scheduling the thread. The priority may be temporarily boosted for an active thread.","pos":[0,198],"nodes":[{"content":"The current priority of the thread, which may deviate from the base priority based on how the operating system is scheduling the thread.","pos":[0,136]},{"content":"The priority may be temporarily boosted for an active thread.","pos":[137,198]}]}]},{"pos":[9281,9322],"content":"Gets the unique identifier of the thread.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Gets the unique identifier of the thread.","pos":[0,41]}]},{"pos":[9334,9444],"content":"The operating system reuses thread identification numbers, which identify threads only during their lifetimes.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The operating system reuses thread identification numbers, which identify threads only during their lifetimes.","pos":[0,110]}]},{"pos":[9547,9603],"content":"The unique identifier associated with a specific thread.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The unique identifier associated with a specific thread.","pos":[0,56]}]},{"pos":[10045,10100],"content":"Sets the preferred processor for this thread to run on.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Sets the preferred processor for this thread to run on.","pos":[0,55]}]},{"pos":[10113,10600],"content":"The IdealProcessor value is zero-based.  In other words, to set the thread affinity for the first processor, set the property to zero.       The system schedules threads on their preferred processors whenever possible.       A process thread can migrate from processor to processor, with each migration reloading the processor cache. Specifying a processor for a thread can improve performance under heavy system loads by reducing the number of times the processor cache is reloaded.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The IdealProcessor value is zero-based.  In other words, to set the thread affinity for the first processor, set the property to zero.       The system schedules threads on their preferred processors whenever possible.       A process thread can migrate from processor to processor, with each migration reloading the processor cache. Specifying a processor for a thread can improve performance under heavy system loads by reducing the number of times the processor cache is reloaded.","pos":[0,483],"nodes":[{"content":"The IdealProcessor value is zero-based.","pos":[0,39]},{"content":"In other words, to set the thread affinity for the first processor, set the property to zero.","pos":[41,134]},{"content":"The system schedules threads on their preferred processors whenever possible.","pos":[141,218]},{"content":"A process thread can migrate from processor to processor, with each migration reloading the processor cache.","pos":[225,333]},{"content":"Specifying a processor for a thread can improve performance under heavy system loads by reducing the number of times the processor cache is reloaded.","pos":[334,483]}]}]},{"pos":[11075,11205],"content":"The preferred processor for the thread, used when the system schedules threads, to determine which processor to run the thread on.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The preferred processor for the thread, used when the system schedules threads, to determine which processor to run the thread on.","pos":[0,130]}]},{"pos":[11399,11471],"content":"The system could not set the thread to start on the specified processor.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The system could not set the thread to start on the specified processor.","pos":[0,72]}]},{"pos":[11590,11647],"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","pos":[0,57]}]},{"pos":[11750,11786],"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","pos":[0,36]}]},{"pos":[12192,12384],"content":"Gets or sets a value indicating whether the operating system should temporarily boost the priority of the associated thread whenever the main window of the thread's process receives the focus.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Gets or sets a value indicating whether the operating system should temporarily boost the priority of the associated thread whenever the main window of the thread's process receives the focus.","pos":[0,192]}]},{"pos":[12397,13420],"content":"When PriorityBoostEnabled is `true`, the system temporarily boosts the thread's priority whenever its associated process is taken out of the wait state. This action prevents other processes from interrupting the processing of the current thread. The PriorityBoostEnabled setting affects all existing threads as well as any threads subsequently created by the process. To restore normal behavior, set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityBoostEnabled%2A> property to `false`.       PriorityBoostEnabled has an effect only when the thread is running in a process that has a <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityClass%2A> set to one of the dynamic priority enumeration values (<xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, or <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>).      > [!NOTE] >  Boosting the priority too high can drain resources from essential operating system and network functions. This could cause problems with other operating system tasks.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"When PriorityBoostEnabled is <ph id=\"ph1\">`true`</ph>, the system temporarily boosts the thread's priority whenever its associated process is taken out of the wait state.","pos":[0,152],"source":"When PriorityBoostEnabled is `true`, the system temporarily boosts the thread's priority whenever its associated process is taken out of the wait state."},{"content":"This action prevents other processes from interrupting the processing of the current thread.","pos":[153,245]},{"content":"The PriorityBoostEnabled setting affects all existing threads as well as any threads subsequently created by the process.","pos":[246,367]},{"content":"To restore normal behavior, set the &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityBoostEnabled%2A&gt; property to <ph id=\"ph1\">`false`</ph>.","pos":[368,482],"source":" To restore normal behavior, set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityBoostEnabled%2A> property to `false`."},{"content":"PriorityBoostEnabled has an effect only when the thread is running in a process that has a &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityClass%2A&gt; set to one of the dynamic priority enumeration values (&lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass&gt;, &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass&gt;, or &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass&gt;).","pos":[489,833],"source":"       PriorityBoostEnabled has an effect only when the thread is running in a process that has a <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityClass%2A> set to one of the dynamic priority enumeration values (<xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, or <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>)."},{"content":"&gt; <ph id=\"ph1\">[!NOTE]</ph> &gt;  Boosting the priority too high can drain resources from essential operating system and network functions.","pos":[839,957],"source":"      > [!NOTE] >  Boosting the priority too high can drain resources from essential operating system and network functions."},{"content":"This could cause problems with other operating system tasks.","pos":[958,1018]}]},{"pos":[13550,13849],"content":"<xref uid=\"langword_csharp_true\" name=\"true\" href=\"\"></xref> to boost the thread's priority when the user interacts with the process's interface; otherwise, <xref uid=\"langword_csharp_false\" name=\"false\" href=\"\"></xref>. The default is <xref uid=\"langword_csharp_false\" name=\"false\" href=\"\"></xref>.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"<bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref uid=\"langword_csharp_true\" name=\"true\" href=\"\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> to boost the thread's priority when the user interacts with the process's interface; otherwise, <bpt id=\"p2\">&lt;xref uid=\"langword_csharp_false\" name=\"false\" href=\"\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p2\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept>.","pos":[0,220],"source":"<xref uid=\"langword_csharp_true\" name=\"true\" href=\"\"></xref> to boost the thread's priority when the user interacts with the process's interface; otherwise, <xref uid=\"langword_csharp_false\" name=\"false\" href=\"\"></xref>."},{"content":"The default is <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref uid=\"langword_csharp_false\" name=\"false\" href=\"\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept>.","pos":[221,299],"source":" The default is <xref uid=\"langword_csharp_false\" name=\"false\" href=\"\"></xref>."}]},{"pos":[14050,14174],"content":"The priority boost information could not be retrieved.       -or-       The priority boost information could not be set.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The priority boost information could not be retrieved.       -or-       The priority boost information could not be set.","pos":[0,120],"nodes":[{"content":"The priority boost information could not be retrieved.","pos":[0,54]},{"content":"-or-       The priority boost information could not be set.","pos":[61,120]}]}]},{"pos":[14294,14351],"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","pos":[0,57]}]},{"pos":[14454,14490],"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","pos":[0,36]}]},{"pos":[14861,14907],"content":"Gets or sets the priority level of the thread.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Gets or sets the priority level of the thread.","pos":[0,46]}]},{"pos":[14919,15195],"content":"The priority level is not a single value, but rather a range of values. The operating system computes the thread's base priority by using the process's <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityClass%2A> to choose a value from the range specified in the PriorityLevel property.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The priority level is not a single value, but rather a range of values. The operating system computes the thread's base priority by using the process's <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityClass%2A> to choose a value from the range specified in the PriorityLevel property.","pos":[0,276],"nodes":[{"content":"The priority level is not a single value, but rather a range of values.","pos":[0,71]},{"content":"The operating system computes the thread's base priority by using the process's &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityClass%2A&gt; to choose a value from the range specified in the PriorityLevel property.","pos":[72,276],"source":" The operating system computes the thread's base priority by using the process's <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityClass%2A> to choose a value from the range specified in the PriorityLevel property."}]}]},{"pos":[15375,15507],"content":"One of the <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Diagnostics.ThreadPriorityLevel\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> values, specifying a range that bounds the thread's priority.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"One of the <xref href=\"System.Diagnostics.ThreadPriorityLevel\"></xref> values, specifying a range that bounds the thread's priority."},{"pos":[15701,15827],"content":"The thread priority level information could not be retrieved.       -or-       The thread priority level could not be set.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The thread priority level information could not be retrieved.       -or-       The thread priority level could not be set.","pos":[0,122],"nodes":[{"content":"The thread priority level information could not be retrieved.","pos":[0,61]},{"content":"-or-       The thread priority level could not be set.","pos":[68,122]}]}]},{"pos":[15947,16004],"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","pos":[0,57]}]},{"pos":[16107,16143],"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","pos":[0,36]}]},{"pos":[16564,16660],"content":"Gets the amount of time that the thread has spent running code inside the operating system core.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Gets the amount of time that the thread has spent running code inside the operating system core.","pos":[0,96]}]},{"pos":[16673,17888],"content":"Windows uses several different protection mechanisms, and at the root of them all is the distinction between user mode and privileged mode. PrivilegedProcessorTime corresponds to the amount of time that the application has spent running in privileged mode, inside the operating system core. The <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime%2A> property indicates the amount of time that the application has spent running code in user mode, outside the system core.       User mode restricts the application in two important ways. First, the application cannot directly access the peripherals, but instead must call the operating system core to get or set peripheral data. The operating system can thus ensure that one application does not destroy peripheral data that is needed by another. Second, the application cannot read or change data that the operating system itself maintains. This restriction prevents applications from either inadvertently or intentionally corrupting the core. If the application needs the operating system to perform an operation, it calls one of the system's routines. Many of these transition into privileged mode, perform the operation, and smoothly return to user mode.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Windows uses several different protection mechanisms, and at the root of them all is the distinction between user mode and privileged mode. PrivilegedProcessorTime corresponds to the amount of time that the application has spent running in privileged mode, inside the operating system core. The <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime%2A> property indicates the amount of time that the application has spent running code in user mode, outside the system core.       User mode restricts the application in two important ways. First, the application cannot directly access the peripherals, but instead must call the operating system core to get or set peripheral data. The operating system can thus ensure that one application does not destroy peripheral data that is needed by another. Second, the application cannot read or change data that the operating system itself maintains. This restriction prevents applications from either inadvertently or intentionally corrupting the core. If the application needs the operating system to perform an operation, it calls one of the system's routines. Many of these transition into privileged mode, perform the operation, and smoothly return to user mode.","pos":[0,1213],"nodes":[{"content":"Windows uses several different protection mechanisms, and at the root of them all is the distinction between user mode and privileged mode.","pos":[0,139]},{"content":"PrivilegedProcessorTime corresponds to the amount of time that the application has spent running in privileged mode, inside the operating system core.","pos":[140,290]},{"content":"The &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime%2A&gt; property indicates the amount of time that the application has spent running code in user mode, outside the system core.","pos":[291,476],"source":" The <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime%2A> property indicates the amount of time that the application has spent running code in user mode, outside the system core."},{"content":"User mode restricts the application in two important ways.","pos":[483,541]},{"content":"First, the application cannot directly access the peripherals, but instead must call the operating system core to get or set peripheral data.","pos":[542,683]},{"content":"The operating system can thus ensure that one application does not destroy peripheral data that is needed by another.","pos":[684,801]},{"content":"Second, the application cannot read or change data that the operating system itself maintains.","pos":[802,896]},{"content":"This restriction prevents applications from either inadvertently or intentionally corrupting the core.","pos":[897,999]},{"content":"If the application needs the operating system to perform an operation, it calls one of the system's routines.","pos":[1000,1109]},{"content":"Many of these transition into privileged mode, perform the operation, and smoothly return to user mode.","pos":[1110,1213]}]}]},{"pos":[18021,18148],"content":"A <xref:System.TimeSpan> indicating the amount of time that the thread has spent running code inside the operating system core.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"A &lt;xref:System.TimeSpan&gt; indicating the amount of time that the thread has spent running code inside the operating system core.","pos":[0,127],"source":"A <xref:System.TimeSpan> indicating the amount of time that the thread has spent running code inside the operating system core."}]},{"pos":[18351,18390],"content":"The thread time could not be retrieved.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The thread time could not be retrieved.","pos":[0,39]}]},{"pos":[18509,18566],"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","pos":[0,57]}]},{"pos":[18669,18705],"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","pos":[0,36]}]},{"pos":[19096,19155],"content":"Sets the processors on which the associated thread can run.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Sets the processors on which the associated thread can run.","pos":[0,59]}]},{"pos":[19168,20212],"content":"The processor affinity of a thread is the set of processors it has a relationship to. In other words, those it can be scheduled to run on.       ProcessorAffinity represents each processor as a bit. Bit 0 represents processor one, bit 1 represents processor two, and so on. The following table shows a subset of the possible ProcessorAffinity for a four-processor system.      |Property value (in hexadecimal)|Valid processors|   |---------------------------------------|----------------------|   |0x0001|1|   |0x0002|2|   |0x0003|1 or 2|   |0x0004|3|   |0x0005|1 or 3|   |0x0007|1, 2, or 3|   |0x000F|1, 2, 3, or 4|       You can also specify the single, preferred processor for a thread by setting the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.IdealProcessor%2A> property. A process thread can migrate from processor to processor, with each migration reloading the processor cache. Specifying a processor for a thread can improve performance under heavy system loads by reducing the number of times the processor cache is reloaded.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The processor affinity of a thread is the set of processors it has a relationship to. In other words, those it can be scheduled to run on.       ProcessorAffinity represents each processor as a bit. Bit 0 represents processor one, bit 1 represents processor two, and so on. The following table shows a subset of the possible ProcessorAffinity for a four-processor system.      |Property value (in hexadecimal)|Valid processors|   |---------------------------------------|----------------------|   |0x0001|1|   |0x0002|2|   |0x0003|1 or 2|   |0x0004|3|   |0x0005|1 or 3|   |0x0007|1, 2, or 3|   |0x000F|1, 2, 3, or 4|       You can also specify the single, preferred processor for a thread by setting the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.IdealProcessor%2A> property. A process thread can migrate from processor to processor, with each migration reloading the processor cache. Specifying a processor for a thread can improve performance under heavy system loads by reducing the number of times the processor cache is reloaded.","pos":[0,1030],"nodes":[{"content":"The processor affinity of a thread is the set of processors it has a relationship to.","pos":[0,85]},{"content":"In other words, those it can be scheduled to run on.","pos":[86,138]},{"content":"ProcessorAffinity represents each processor as a bit.","pos":[145,198]},{"content":"Bit 0 represents processor one, bit 1 represents processor two, and so on.","pos":[199,273]},{"content":"The following table shows a subset of the possible ProcessorAffinity for a four-processor system.","pos":[274,371]},{"content":"|Property value (in hexadecimal)|Valid processors|   |---------------------------------------|----------------------|   |0x0001|1|   |0x0002|2|   |0x0003|1 or 2|   |0x0004|3|   |0x0005|1 or 3|   |0x0007|1, 2, or 3|   |0x000F|1, 2, 3, or 4|       You can also specify the single, preferred processor for a thread by setting the &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.IdealProcessor%2A&gt; property.","pos":[377,771],"source":"      |Property value (in hexadecimal)|Valid processors|   |---------------------------------------|----------------------|   |0x0001|1|   |0x0002|2|   |0x0003|1 or 2|   |0x0004|3|   |0x0005|1 or 3|   |0x0007|1, 2, or 3|   |0x000F|1, 2, 3, or 4|       You can also specify the single, preferred processor for a thread by setting the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.IdealProcessor%2A> property."},{"content":"A process thread can migrate from processor to processor, with each migration reloading the processor cache.","pos":[772,880]},{"content":"Specifying a processor for a thread can improve performance under heavy system loads by reducing the number of times the processor cache is reloaded.","pos":[881,1030]}]}]},{"pos":[20690,20808],"content":"An <xref:System.IntPtr> that points to a set of bits, each of which represents a processor that the thread can run on.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"An &lt;xref:System.IntPtr&gt; that points to a set of bits, each of which represents a processor that the thread can run on.","pos":[0,118],"source":"An <xref:System.IntPtr> that points to a set of bits, each of which represents a processor that the thread can run on."}]},{"pos":[21005,21045],"content":"The processor affinity could not be set.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The processor affinity could not be set.","pos":[0,40]}]},{"pos":[21164,21221],"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","pos":[0,57]}]},{"pos":[21324,21360],"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","pos":[0,36]}]},{"pos":[21765,21908],"content":"Resets the ideal processor for this thread to indicate that there is no single ideal processor. In other words, so that any processor is ideal.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Resets the ideal processor for this thread to indicate that there is no single ideal processor. In other words, so that any processor is ideal.","pos":[0,143],"nodes":[{"content":"Resets the ideal processor for this thread to indicate that there is no single ideal processor.","pos":[0,95]},{"content":"In other words, so that any processor is ideal.","pos":[96,143]}]}]},{"pos":[22185,22224],"content":"The ideal processor could not be reset.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The ideal processor could not be reset.","pos":[0,39]}]},{"pos":[22343,22400],"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","pos":[0,57]}]},{"pos":[22503,22539],"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","pos":[0,36]}]},{"pos":[22905,23003],"content":"Gets the memory address of the function that the operating system called that started this thread.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Gets the memory address of the function that the operating system called that started this thread.","pos":[0,98]}]},{"pos":[23016,24175],"content":"Each process starts with a single thread, which is known as the primary thread. Any thread can create additional threads.       A process has a virtual address space, executable code, data, object handles, environment variables, a base priority, and minimum and maximum working set sizes. All the threads of a process share its virtual address space and system resources. In addition, each thread maintains exception handlers, a scheduling priority, and a set of structures in which the system saves the thread context while the thread is waiting to be scheduled. The thread context includes the thread's set of machine registers, the kernel stack, a thread environment block, and a user stack in the address space of the thread's process.       Every Windows thread actually begins execution in a system-supplied function, not the application-supplied function. The starting address for the primary thread is, therefore, the same (as it represents the address of the system-supplied function) for every Windows process in the system. However, the StartAddress property allows you to get the starting function address that is specific to your application.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Each process starts with a single thread, which is known as the primary thread. Any thread can create additional threads.       A process has a virtual address space, executable code, data, object handles, environment variables, a base priority, and minimum and maximum working set sizes. All the threads of a process share its virtual address space and system resources. In addition, each thread maintains exception handlers, a scheduling priority, and a set of structures in which the system saves the thread context while the thread is waiting to be scheduled. The thread context includes the thread's set of machine registers, the kernel stack, a thread environment block, and a user stack in the address space of the thread's process.       Every Windows thread actually begins execution in a system-supplied function, not the application-supplied function. The starting address for the primary thread is, therefore, the same (as it represents the address of the system-supplied function) for every Windows process in the system. However, the StartAddress property allows you to get the starting function address that is specific to your application.","pos":[0,1155],"nodes":[{"content":"Each process starts with a single thread, which is known as the primary thread.","pos":[0,79]},{"content":"Any thread can create additional threads.","pos":[80,121]},{"content":"A process has a virtual address space, executable code, data, object handles, environment variables, a base priority, and minimum and maximum working set sizes.","pos":[128,288]},{"content":"All the threads of a process share its virtual address space and system resources.","pos":[289,371]},{"content":"In addition, each thread maintains exception handlers, a scheduling priority, and a set of structures in which the system saves the thread context while the thread is waiting to be scheduled.","pos":[372,563]},{"content":"The thread context includes the thread's set of machine registers, the kernel stack, a thread environment block, and a user stack in the address space of the thread's process.","pos":[564,739]},{"content":"Every Windows thread actually begins execution in a system-supplied function, not the application-supplied function.","pos":[746,862]},{"content":"The starting address for the primary thread is, therefore, the same (as it represents the address of the system-supplied function) for every Windows process in the system.","pos":[863,1034]},{"content":"However, the StartAddress property allows you to get the starting function address that is specific to your application.","pos":[1035,1155]}]}]},{"pos":[24293,24398],"content":"The thread's starting address, which points to the application-defined function that the thread executes.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The thread's starting address, which points to the application-defined function that the thread executes.","pos":[0,105]}]},{"pos":[24590,24647],"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","pos":[0,57]}]},{"pos":[24750,24786],"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","pos":[0,36]}]},{"pos":[25137,25196],"content":"Gets the time that the operating system started the thread.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Gets the time that the operating system started the thread.","pos":[0,59]}]},{"pos":[25314,25429],"content":"A <xref:System.DateTime> representing the time that was on the system when the operating system started the thread.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"A &lt;xref:System.DateTime&gt; representing the time that was on the system when the operating system started the thread.","pos":[0,115],"source":"A <xref:System.DateTime> representing the time that was on the system when the operating system started the thread."}]},{"pos":[25618,25657],"content":"The thread time could not be retrieved.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The thread time could not be retrieved.","pos":[0,39]}]},{"pos":[25776,25833],"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","pos":[0,57]}]},{"pos":[25936,25972],"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","pos":[0,36]}]},{"pos":[26333,26371],"content":"Gets the current state of this thread.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Gets the current state of this thread.","pos":[0,38]}]},{"pos":[26383,26660],"content":"The <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason%2A> property value is valid only when the ThreadState value is <xref:System.Diagnostics.ThreadState>. Therefore, check the ThreadState value before you get the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason%2A> property.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason%2A> property value is valid only when the ThreadState value is <xref:System.Diagnostics.ThreadState>. Therefore, check the ThreadState value before you get the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason%2A> property.","pos":[0,277],"nodes":[{"content":"The &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason%2A&gt; property value is valid only when the ThreadState value is &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ThreadState&gt;.","pos":[0,155],"source":"The <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason%2A> property value is valid only when the ThreadState value is <xref:System.Diagnostics.ThreadState>."},{"content":"Therefore, check the ThreadState value before you get the &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason%2A&gt; property.","pos":[156,277],"source":" Therefore, check the ThreadState value before you get the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason%2A> property."}]}]},{"pos":[26817,26955],"content":"A <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Diagnostics.ThreadState\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> that indicates the thread's execution, for example, running, waiting, or terminated.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"A <xref href=\"System.Diagnostics.ThreadState\"></xref> that indicates the thread's execution, for example, running, waiting, or terminated."},{"pos":[27146,27203],"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","pos":[0,57]}]},{"pos":[27306,27342],"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","pos":[0,36]}]},{"pos":[27738,27815],"content":"Gets the total amount of time that this thread has spent using the processor.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Gets the total amount of time that this thread has spent using the processor.","pos":[0,77]}]},{"pos":[27828,28326],"content":"The TotalProcessorTime property indicates the total amount of time that the system has taken the thread out of the wait state and given it priority on any processor. On a multiple processor system, this value would include time spent on each processor, if the thread used more than one processor.       The TotalProcessorTime property is the sum of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime%2A> and <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime%2A> properties.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The TotalProcessorTime property indicates the total amount of time that the system has taken the thread out of the wait state and given it priority on any processor. On a multiple processor system, this value would include time spent on each processor, if the thread used more than one processor.       The TotalProcessorTime property is the sum of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime%2A> and <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime%2A> properties.","pos":[0,496],"nodes":[{"content":"The TotalProcessorTime property indicates the total amount of time that the system has taken the thread out of the wait state and given it priority on any processor.","pos":[0,165]},{"content":"On a multiple processor system, this value would include time spent on each processor, if the thread used more than one processor.","pos":[166,296]},{"content":"The TotalProcessorTime property is the sum of the &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime%2A&gt; and &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime%2A&gt; properties.","pos":[303,496],"source":"       The TotalProcessorTime property is the sum of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime%2A> and <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime%2A> properties."}]}]},{"pos":[28454,28562],"content":"A <xref:System.TimeSpan> that indicates the amount of time that the thread has had control of the processor.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"A &lt;xref:System.TimeSpan&gt; that indicates the amount of time that the thread has had control of the processor.","pos":[0,108],"source":"A <xref:System.TimeSpan> that indicates the amount of time that the thread has had control of the processor."}]},{"pos":[28760,28799],"content":"The thread time could not be retrieved.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The thread time could not be retrieved.","pos":[0,39]}]},{"pos":[28918,28975],"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","pos":[0,57]}]},{"pos":[29078,29114],"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","pos":[0,36]}]},{"pos":[29505,29602],"content":"Gets the amount of time that the associated thread has spent running code inside the application.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Gets the amount of time that the associated thread has spent running code inside the application.","pos":[0,97]}]},{"pos":[29615,30829],"content":"Windows NT uses several different protection mechanisms, and at the root of them all is the distinction between user mode and privileged mode. UserProcessorTime corresponds to the amount of time that the application has spent running in user mode, outside the operating system core. The <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime%2A> corresponds to the amount of time that the application has spent running code in privileged mode, inside the system core.       User mode restricts the application in two important ways. First, the application cannot directly access the peripherals, but instead must call the operating system core to get or set peripheral data. The operating system can thus ensure that one application does not destroy peripheral data that is needed by another. Second, the application cannot read or change data that the operating system itself maintains. This restriction prevents applications from either inadvertently or intentionally corrupting the core. If the application needs the operating system to perform an operation, it calls one of the system's routines. Many of these transition into privileged mode, perform the operation, and smoothly return to user mode.","needQuote":false,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Windows NT uses several different protection mechanisms, and at the root of them all is the distinction between user mode and privileged mode. UserProcessorTime corresponds to the amount of time that the application has spent running in user mode, outside the operating system core. The <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime%2A> corresponds to the amount of time that the application has spent running code in privileged mode, inside the system core.       User mode restricts the application in two important ways. First, the application cannot directly access the peripherals, but instead must call the operating system core to get or set peripheral data. The operating system can thus ensure that one application does not destroy peripheral data that is needed by another. Second, the application cannot read or change data that the operating system itself maintains. This restriction prevents applications from either inadvertently or intentionally corrupting the core. If the application needs the operating system to perform an operation, it calls one of the system's routines. Many of these transition into privileged mode, perform the operation, and smoothly return to user mode.","pos":[0,1212],"nodes":[{"content":"Windows NT uses several different protection mechanisms, and at the root of them all is the distinction between user mode and privileged mode.","pos":[0,142]},{"content":"UserProcessorTime corresponds to the amount of time that the application has spent running in user mode, outside the operating system core.","pos":[143,282]},{"content":"The &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime%2A&gt; corresponds to the amount of time that the application has spent running code in privileged mode, inside the system core.","pos":[283,475],"source":" The <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime%2A> corresponds to the amount of time that the application has spent running code in privileged mode, inside the system core."},{"content":"User mode restricts the application in two important ways.","pos":[482,540]},{"content":"First, the application cannot directly access the peripherals, but instead must call the operating system core to get or set peripheral data.","pos":[541,682]},{"content":"The operating system can thus ensure that one application does not destroy peripheral data that is needed by another.","pos":[683,800]},{"content":"Second, the application cannot read or change data that the operating system itself maintains.","pos":[801,895]},{"content":"This restriction prevents applications from either inadvertently or intentionally corrupting the core.","pos":[896,998]},{"content":"If the application needs the operating system to perform an operation, it calls one of the system's routines.","pos":[999,1108]},{"content":"Many of these transition into privileged mode, perform the operation, and smoothly return to user mode.","pos":[1109,1212]}]}]},{"pos":[30956,31121],"content":"A <xref:System.TimeSpan> indicating the amount of time that the thread has spent running code inside the application, as opposed to inside the operating system core.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"A &lt;xref:System.TimeSpan&gt; indicating the amount of time that the thread has spent running code inside the application, as opposed to inside the operating system core.","pos":[0,165],"source":"A <xref:System.TimeSpan> indicating the amount of time that the thread has spent running code inside the application, as opposed to inside the operating system core."}]},{"pos":[31318,31357],"content":"The thread time could not be retrieved.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The thread time could not be retrieved.","pos":[0,39]}]},{"pos":[31476,31533],"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","pos":[0,57]}]},{"pos":[31636,31672],"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","pos":[0,36]}]},{"pos":[32028,32071],"content":"Gets the reason that the thread is waiting.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Gets the reason that the thread is waiting.","pos":[0,43]}]},{"pos":[32083,32348],"content":"The WaitReason property is valid only when the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState%2A> is <xref:System.Diagnostics.ThreadState>. Therefore, check the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState%2A> value before you get the WaitReason property.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The WaitReason property is valid only when the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState%2A> is <xref:System.Diagnostics.ThreadState>. Therefore, check the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState%2A> value before you get the WaitReason property.","pos":[0,265],"nodes":[{"content":"The WaitReason property is valid only when the &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState%2A&gt; is &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ThreadState&gt;.","pos":[0,143],"source":"The WaitReason property is valid only when the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState%2A> is <xref:System.Diagnostics.ThreadState>."},{"content":"Therefore, check the &lt;xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState%2A&gt; value before you get the WaitReason property.","pos":[144,265],"source":" Therefore, check the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState%2A> value before you get the WaitReason property."}]}]},{"pos":[32514,32634],"content":"A <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.Diagnostics.ThreadWaitReason\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> representing the reason that the thread is in the wait state.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"A <xref href=\"System.Diagnostics.ThreadWaitReason\"></xref> representing the reason that the thread is in the wait state."},{"pos":[32816,32852],"content":"The thread is not in the wait state.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The thread is not in the wait state.","pos":[0,36]}]},{"pos":[32971,33028],"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.","pos":[0,57]}]},{"pos":[33131,33167],"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The process is on a remote computer.","pos":[0,36]}]}],"content":"### YamlMime:ManagedReference\nitems:\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  id: ProcessThread\n  children:\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.BasePriority\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.CurrentPriority\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.Id\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.IdealProcessor\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityBoostEnabled\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityLevel\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ProcessorAffinity\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ResetIdealProcessor\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.StartAddress\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.StartTime\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.TotalProcessorTime\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime\n  - System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: ProcessThread\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  type: Class\n  summary: Represents an operating system process thread.\n  remarks: \"Use ProcessThread to obtain information about a thread that is currently running on the system. Doing so allows you, for example, to monitor the thread's performance characteristics.  \\n  \\n> [!IMPORTANT]\\n>  This type implements the <xref:System.IDisposable> interface. When you have finished using the type, you should dispose of it either directly or indirectly. To dispose of the type directly, call its <xref:System.IDisposable.Dispose%2A> method in a `try`/`catch` block. To dispose of it indirectly, use a language construct such as `using` (in C#) or `Using` (in Visual Basic). For more information, see the “Using an Object that Implements IDisposable” section in the <xref:System.IDisposable> interface topic.  \\n  \\n A thread is a path of execution through a program. It is the smallest unit of execution that Win32 schedules. It consists of a stack, the state of the CPU registers, and an entry in the execution list of the system scheduler.  \\n  \\n A process consists of one or more threads and the code, data, and other resources of a program in memory. Typical program resources are open files, semaphores, and dynamically allocated memory. Each resource of a process is shared by all that process's threads.  \\n  \\n A program executes when the system scheduler gives execution control to one of the program's threads. The scheduler determines which threads should run and when. A lower-priority thread might be forced to wait while higher-priority threads complete their tasks. On multiprocessor computers, the scheduler can move individual threads to different processors, thus balancing the CPU load.  \\n  \\n Each process starts with a single thread, which is known as the primary thread. Any thread can create additional threads. All the threads within a process share the address space of that process.  \\n  \\n The primary thread is not necessarily located at the first index in the collection.  \\n  \\n> [!NOTE]\\n>  Starting with the .NET Framework version 2.0, the ability to reference performance counter data on other computers has been eliminated for many of the .NET Framework methods and properties. This change was made to improve performance and to enable non-administrators to use the ProcessThread class. As a result, some applications that did not get exceptions in earlier versions of the .NET Framework may now get a <xref:System.NotSupportedException>. The methods and properties affected are too numerous to list here, but the exception information has been added to the affected member topics.  \\n  \\n The threads of a process execute individually and are unaware of each other unless you make them visible to each other. Threads that share common resources, however, must coordinate their work by using semaphores or another method of interprocess communication.  \\n  \\n To get a collection of all the ProcessThread objects associated with the current process, get the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.Threads%2A> property of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process> instance.\"\n  syntax:\n    content: >-\n      [System.ComponentModel.Designer(\"System.Diagnostics.Design.ProcessThreadDesigner, System.Design, Version=4.0.0.0, Culture=neutral, PublicKeyToken=b03f5f7f11d50a3a\")]\n\n      public class ProcessThread : System.ComponentModel.Component\n  inheritance:\n  - System.Object\n  - System.MarshalByRefObject\n  - System.ComponentModel.Component\n  implements: []\n  inheritedMembers:\n  - System.ComponentModel.Component.CanRaiseEvents\n  - System.ComponentModel.Component.Container\n  - System.ComponentModel.Component.DesignMode\n  - System.ComponentModel.Component.Dispose\n  - System.ComponentModel.Component.Dispose(System.Boolean)\n  - System.ComponentModel.Component.Disposed\n  - System.ComponentModel.Component.Events\n  - System.ComponentModel.Component.GetService(System.Type)\n  - System.ComponentModel.Component.Site\n  - System.ComponentModel.Component.ToString\n  - System.MarshalByRefObject.CreateObjRef(System.Type)\n  - System.MarshalByRefObject.GetLifetimeService\n  - System.MarshalByRefObject.InitializeLifetimeService\n  - System.MarshalByRefObject.MemberwiseClone(System.Boolean)\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.BasePriority\n  id: BasePriority\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: BasePriority\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.BasePriority\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.BasePriority\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Gets the base priority of the thread.\n  remarks: \"The BasePriority is the starting priority for the process thread. You can view information about the base priority through the System Monitor's Priority Base counter.  \\n  \\n The operating system computes a thread's base priority by combining the thread's priority level range with the process's priority class. You can set the process's <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityClass%2A?displayProperty=fullName> property to one of the values in the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass> enumeration, which are <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, or <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>. You can set the thread's <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityLevel%2A> property to a range of values that bounds the thread's base priority. Win32 uses four priority classes with seven base priority levels per class.  \\n  \\n The thread's current priority might deviate from the base priority. For example, the operating system can change the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.CurrentPriority%2A> property based on the time elapsed or other boosts when a process must be put ahead of others for access to the processor. In addition, you can set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityBoostEnabled%2A> property to cause the system to temporarily boost the priority of a thread whenever the process is taken out of the wait state. The priority is reset when the process returns to the wait state.\"\n  syntax:\n    content: public int BasePriority { get; }\n    return:\n      type: System.Int32\n      description: The base priority of the thread, which the operating system computes by combining the process priority class with the priority level of the associated thread.\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.BasePriority*\n  exceptions: []\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.CurrentPriority\n  id: CurrentPriority\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: CurrentPriority\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.CurrentPriority\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.CurrentPriority\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Gets the current priority of the thread.\n  remarks: The thread's current priority might deviate from the base priority. For example, the operating system can change the CurrentPriority property based on the time elapsed, or other boosts, when a process must be put ahead of others for access to the processor. In addition, you can set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityBoostEnabled%2A> property to cause the system to temporarily boost the priority of a thread whenever the process is taken out of the wait state. The priority is reset when the process returns to the wait state.\n  syntax:\n    content: public int CurrentPriority { get; }\n    return:\n      type: System.Int32\n      description: The current priority of the thread, which may deviate from the base priority based on how the operating system is scheduling the thread. The priority may be temporarily boosted for an active thread.\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.CurrentPriority*\n  exceptions: []\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.Id\n  id: Id\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: Id\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.Id\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.Id\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Gets the unique identifier of the thread.\n  remarks: The operating system reuses thread identification numbers, which identify threads only during their lifetimes.\n  syntax:\n    content: public int Id { get; }\n    return:\n      type: System.Int32\n      description: The unique identifier associated with a specific thread.\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.Id*\n  exceptions: []\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.IdealProcessor\n  id: IdealProcessor\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: IdealProcessor\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.IdealProcessor\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.IdealProcessor\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Sets the preferred processor for this thread to run on.\n  remarks: \"The IdealProcessor value is zero-based.  In other words, to set the thread affinity for the first processor, set the property to zero.  \\n  \\n The system schedules threads on their preferred processors whenever possible.  \\n  \\n A process thread can migrate from processor to processor, with each migration reloading the processor cache. Specifying a processor for a thread can improve performance under heavy system loads by reducing the number of times the processor cache is reloaded.\"\n  example:\n  - \"The following example demonstrates how to set the IdealProcessor property for an instance of Notepad to the first processor.  \\n  \\n [!code-vb[ProcessThreadIdealProcessor#1](~/add/codesnippet/visualbasic/p-system.diagnostics.pro_25_1.vb)]\\n [!code-cs[ProcessThreadIdealProcessor#1](~/add/codesnippet/csharp/p-system.diagnostics.pro_25_1.cs)]\"\n  syntax:\n    content: public int IdealProcessor { set; }\n    return:\n      type: System.Int32\n      description: The preferred processor for the thread, used when the system schedules threads, to determine which processor to run the thread on.\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.IdealProcessor*\n  exceptions:\n  - type: System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    commentId: T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    description: The system could not set the thread to start on the specified processor.\n  - type: System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    description: The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.\n  - type: System.NotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.NotSupportedException\n    description: The process is on a remote computer.\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityBoostEnabled\n  id: PriorityBoostEnabled\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: PriorityBoostEnabled\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.PriorityBoostEnabled\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityBoostEnabled\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Gets or sets a value indicating whether the operating system should temporarily boost the priority of the associated thread whenever the main window of the thread's process receives the focus.\n  remarks: \"When PriorityBoostEnabled is `true`, the system temporarily boosts the thread's priority whenever its associated process is taken out of the wait state. This action prevents other processes from interrupting the processing of the current thread. The PriorityBoostEnabled setting affects all existing threads as well as any threads subsequently created by the process. To restore normal behavior, set the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityBoostEnabled%2A> property to `false`.  \\n  \\n PriorityBoostEnabled has an effect only when the thread is running in a process that has a <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityClass%2A> set to one of the dynamic priority enumeration values (<xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>, or <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessPriorityClass>).  \\n  \\n> [!NOTE]\\n>  Boosting the priority too high can drain resources from essential operating system and network functions. This could cause problems with other operating system tasks.\"\n  syntax:\n    content: public bool PriorityBoostEnabled { get; set; }\n    return:\n      type: System.Boolean\n      description: <xref uid=\"langword_csharp_true\" name=\"true\" href=\"\"></xref> to boost the thread's priority when the user interacts with the process's interface; otherwise, <xref uid=\"langword_csharp_false\" name=\"false\" href=\"\"></xref>. The default is <xref uid=\"langword_csharp_false\" name=\"false\" href=\"\"></xref>.\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityBoostEnabled*\n  exceptions:\n  - type: System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    commentId: T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    description: \"The priority boost information could not be retrieved.  \\n  \\n -or-  \\n  \\n The priority boost information could not be set.\"\n  - type: System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    description: The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.\n  - type: System.NotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.NotSupportedException\n    description: The process is on a remote computer.\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityLevel\n  id: PriorityLevel\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: PriorityLevel\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.PriorityLevel\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityLevel\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Gets or sets the priority level of the thread.\n  remarks: The priority level is not a single value, but rather a range of values. The operating system computes the thread's base priority by using the process's <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process.PriorityClass%2A> to choose a value from the range specified in the PriorityLevel property.\n  syntax:\n    content: public System.Diagnostics.ThreadPriorityLevel PriorityLevel { get; set; }\n    return:\n      type: System.Diagnostics.ThreadPriorityLevel\n      description: One of the <xref href=\"System.Diagnostics.ThreadPriorityLevel\"></xref> values, specifying a range that bounds the thread's priority.\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityLevel*\n  exceptions:\n  - type: System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    commentId: T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    description: \"The thread priority level information could not be retrieved.  \\n  \\n -or-  \\n  \\n The thread priority level could not be set.\"\n  - type: System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    description: The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.\n  - type: System.NotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.NotSupportedException\n    description: The process is on a remote computer.\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime\n  id: PrivilegedProcessorTime\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: PrivilegedProcessorTime\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Gets the amount of time that the thread has spent running code inside the operating system core.\n  remarks: \"Windows uses several different protection mechanisms, and at the root of them all is the distinction between user mode and privileged mode. PrivilegedProcessorTime corresponds to the amount of time that the application has spent running in privileged mode, inside the operating system core. The <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime%2A> property indicates the amount of time that the application has spent running code in user mode, outside the system core.  \\n  \\n User mode restricts the application in two important ways. First, the application cannot directly access the peripherals, but instead must call the operating system core to get or set peripheral data. The operating system can thus ensure that one application does not destroy peripheral data that is needed by another. Second, the application cannot read or change data that the operating system itself maintains. This restriction prevents applications from either inadvertently or intentionally corrupting the core. If the application needs the operating system to perform an operation, it calls one of the system's routines. Many of these transition into privileged mode, perform the operation, and smoothly return to user mode.\"\n  syntax:\n    content: public TimeSpan PrivilegedProcessorTime { get; }\n    return:\n      type: System.TimeSpan\n      description: A <xref:System.TimeSpan> indicating the amount of time that the thread has spent running code inside the operating system core.\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime*\n  exceptions:\n  - type: System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    commentId: T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    description: The thread time could not be retrieved.\n  - type: System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    description: The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.\n  - type: System.NotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.NotSupportedException\n    description: The process is on a remote computer.\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ProcessorAffinity\n  id: ProcessorAffinity\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: ProcessorAffinity\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.ProcessorAffinity\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ProcessorAffinity\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Sets the processors on which the associated thread can run.\n  remarks: \"The processor affinity of a thread is the set of processors it has a relationship to. In other words, those it can be scheduled to run on.  \\n  \\n ProcessorAffinity represents each processor as a bit. Bit 0 represents processor one, bit 1 represents processor two, and so on. The following table shows a subset of the possible ProcessorAffinity for a four-processor system.  \\n  \\n|Property value (in hexadecimal)|Valid processors|  \\n|---------------------------------------|----------------------|  \\n|0x0001|1|  \\n|0x0002|2|  \\n|0x0003|1 or 2|  \\n|0x0004|3|  \\n|0x0005|1 or 3|  \\n|0x0007|1, 2, or 3|  \\n|0x000F|1, 2, 3, or 4|  \\n  \\n You can also specify the single, preferred processor for a thread by setting the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.IdealProcessor%2A> property. A process thread can migrate from processor to processor, with each migration reloading the processor cache. Specifying a processor for a thread can improve performance under heavy system loads by reducing the number of times the processor cache is reloaded.\"\n  example:\n  - \"The following example shows how to set the ProcessorAffinity property for an instance of Notepad to the first processor.  \\n  \\n [!code-vb[ProcessThreadIdealProcessor#1](~/add/codesnippet/visualbasic/p-system.diagnostics.pro_22_1.vb)]\\n [!code-cs[ProcessThreadIdealProcessor#1](~/add/codesnippet/csharp/p-system.diagnostics.pro_22_1.cs)]\"\n  syntax:\n    content: public IntPtr ProcessorAffinity { set; }\n    return:\n      type: System.IntPtr\n      description: An <xref:System.IntPtr> that points to a set of bits, each of which represents a processor that the thread can run on.\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ProcessorAffinity*\n  exceptions:\n  - type: System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    commentId: T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    description: The processor affinity could not be set.\n  - type: System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    description: The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.\n  - type: System.NotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.NotSupportedException\n    description: The process is on a remote computer.\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ResetIdealProcessor\n  id: ResetIdealProcessor\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: ResetIdealProcessor()\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.ResetIdealProcessor()\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ResetIdealProcessor()\n  type: Method\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Resets the ideal processor for this thread to indicate that there is no single ideal processor. In other words, so that any processor is ideal.\n  syntax:\n    content: public void ResetIdealProcessor ();\n    parameters: []\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ResetIdealProcessor*\n  exceptions:\n  - type: System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    commentId: T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    description: The ideal processor could not be reset.\n  - type: System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    description: The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.\n  - type: System.NotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.NotSupportedException\n    description: The process is on a remote computer.\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.StartAddress\n  id: StartAddress\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: StartAddress\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.StartAddress\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.StartAddress\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Gets the memory address of the function that the operating system called that started this thread.\n  remarks: \"Each process starts with a single thread, which is known as the primary thread. Any thread can create additional threads.  \\n  \\n A process has a virtual address space, executable code, data, object handles, environment variables, a base priority, and minimum and maximum working set sizes. All the threads of a process share its virtual address space and system resources. In addition, each thread maintains exception handlers, a scheduling priority, and a set of structures in which the system saves the thread context while the thread is waiting to be scheduled. The thread context includes the thread's set of machine registers, the kernel stack, a thread environment block, and a user stack in the address space of the thread's process.  \\n  \\n Every Windows thread actually begins execution in a system-supplied function, not the application-supplied function. The starting address for the primary thread is, therefore, the same (as it represents the address of the system-supplied function) for every Windows process in the system. However, the StartAddress property allows you to get the starting function address that is specific to your application.\"\n  syntax:\n    content: public IntPtr StartAddress { get; }\n    return:\n      type: System.IntPtr\n      description: The thread's starting address, which points to the application-defined function that the thread executes.\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.StartAddress*\n  exceptions:\n  - type: System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    description: The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.\n  - type: System.NotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.NotSupportedException\n    description: The process is on a remote computer.\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.StartTime\n  id: StartTime\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: StartTime\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.StartTime\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.StartTime\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Gets the time that the operating system started the thread.\n  syntax:\n    content: public DateTime StartTime { get; }\n    return:\n      type: System.DateTime\n      description: A <xref:System.DateTime> representing the time that was on the system when the operating system started the thread.\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.StartTime*\n  exceptions:\n  - type: System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    commentId: T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    description: The thread time could not be retrieved.\n  - type: System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    description: The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.\n  - type: System.NotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.NotSupportedException\n    description: The process is on a remote computer.\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState\n  id: ThreadState\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: ThreadState\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.ThreadState\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Gets the current state of this thread.\n  remarks: The <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason%2A> property value is valid only when the ThreadState value is <xref:System.Diagnostics.ThreadState>. Therefore, check the ThreadState value before you get the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason%2A> property.\n  syntax:\n    content: public System.Diagnostics.ThreadState ThreadState { get; }\n    return:\n      type: System.Diagnostics.ThreadState\n      description: A <xref href=\"System.Diagnostics.ThreadState\"></xref> that indicates the thread's execution, for example, running, waiting, or terminated.\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState*\n  exceptions:\n  - type: System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    description: The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.\n  - type: System.NotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.NotSupportedException\n    description: The process is on a remote computer.\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.TotalProcessorTime\n  id: TotalProcessorTime\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: TotalProcessorTime\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.TotalProcessorTime\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.TotalProcessorTime\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Gets the total amount of time that this thread has spent using the processor.\n  remarks: \"The TotalProcessorTime property indicates the total amount of time that the system has taken the thread out of the wait state and given it priority on any processor. On a multiple processor system, this value would include time spent on each processor, if the thread used more than one processor.  \\n  \\n The TotalProcessorTime property is the sum of the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime%2A> and <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime%2A> properties.\"\n  syntax:\n    content: public TimeSpan TotalProcessorTime { get; }\n    return:\n      type: System.TimeSpan\n      description: A <xref:System.TimeSpan> that indicates the amount of time that the thread has had control of the processor.\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.TotalProcessorTime*\n  exceptions:\n  - type: System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    commentId: T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    description: The thread time could not be retrieved.\n  - type: System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    description: The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.\n  - type: System.NotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.NotSupportedException\n    description: The process is on a remote computer.\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime\n  id: UserProcessorTime\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: UserProcessorTime\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Gets the amount of time that the associated thread has spent running code inside the application.\n  remarks: \"Windows NT uses several different protection mechanisms, and at the root of them all is the distinction between user mode and privileged mode. UserProcessorTime corresponds to the amount of time that the application has spent running in user mode, outside the operating system core. The <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime%2A> corresponds to the amount of time that the application has spent running code in privileged mode, inside the system core.  \\n  \\n User mode restricts the application in two important ways. First, the application cannot directly access the peripherals, but instead must call the operating system core to get or set peripheral data. The operating system can thus ensure that one application does not destroy peripheral data that is needed by another. Second, the application cannot read or change data that the operating system itself maintains. This restriction prevents applications from either inadvertently or intentionally corrupting the core. If the application needs the operating system to perform an operation, it calls one of the system's routines. Many of these transition into privileged mode, perform the operation, and smoothly return to user mode.\"\n  syntax:\n    content: public TimeSpan UserProcessorTime { get; }\n    return:\n      type: System.TimeSpan\n      description: A <xref:System.TimeSpan> indicating the amount of time that the thread has spent running code inside the application, as opposed to inside the operating system core.\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime*\n  exceptions:\n  - type: System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    commentId: T:System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n    description: The thread time could not be retrieved.\n  - type: System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    description: The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.\n  - type: System.NotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.NotSupportedException\n    description: The process is on a remote computer.\n  platform:\n  - net462\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason\n  id: WaitReason\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: WaitReason\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.WaitReason\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason\n  type: Property\n  assemblies:\n  - System\n  namespace: System.Diagnostics\n  summary: Gets the reason that the thread is waiting.\n  remarks: The WaitReason property is valid only when the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState%2A> is <xref:System.Diagnostics.ThreadState>. Therefore, check the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState%2A> value before you get the WaitReason property.\n  syntax:\n    content: public System.Diagnostics.ThreadWaitReason WaitReason { get; }\n    return:\n      type: System.Diagnostics.ThreadWaitReason\n      description: A <xref href=\"System.Diagnostics.ThreadWaitReason\"></xref> representing the reason that the thread is in the wait state.\n  overload: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason*\n  exceptions:\n  - type: System.InvalidOperationException\n    commentId: T:System.InvalidOperationException\n    description: The thread is not in the wait state.\n  - type: System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n    description: The platform is Windows 98 or Windows Millennium Edition.\n  - type: System.NotSupportedException\n    commentId: T:System.NotSupportedException\n    description: The process is on a remote computer.\n  platform:\n  - net462\nreferences:\n- uid: System.ComponentModel.Component\n  isExternal: false\n  name: System.ComponentModel.Component\n- uid: System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n  parent: System.ComponentModel\n  isExternal: false\n  name: Win32Exception\n  nameWithType: Win32Exception\n  fullName: System.ComponentModel.Win32Exception\n- uid: System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n  isExternal: true\n  name: System.PlatformNotSupportedException\n- uid: System.NotSupportedException\n  isExternal: true\n  name: System.NotSupportedException\n- uid: System.InvalidOperationException\n  isExternal: true\n  name: System.InvalidOperationException\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.BasePriority\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: BasePriority\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.BasePriority\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.BasePriority\n- uid: System.Int32\n  parent: System\n  isExternal: true\n  name: Int32\n  nameWithType: Int32\n  fullName: System.Int32\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.CurrentPriority\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: CurrentPriority\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.CurrentPriority\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.CurrentPriority\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.Id\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: Id\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.Id\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.Id\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.IdealProcessor\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: IdealProcessor\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.IdealProcessor\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.IdealProcessor\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityBoostEnabled\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: PriorityBoostEnabled\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.PriorityBoostEnabled\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityBoostEnabled\n- uid: System.Boolean\n  parent: System\n  isExternal: true\n  name: Boolean\n  nameWithType: Boolean\n  fullName: System.Boolean\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityLevel\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: PriorityLevel\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.PriorityLevel\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityLevel\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ThreadPriorityLevel\n  parent: System.Diagnostics\n  isExternal: false\n  name: ThreadPriorityLevel\n  nameWithType: ThreadPriorityLevel\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ThreadPriorityLevel\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: PrivilegedProcessorTime\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime\n- uid: System.TimeSpan\n  parent: System\n  isExternal: true\n  name: TimeSpan\n  nameWithType: TimeSpan\n  fullName: System.TimeSpan\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ProcessorAffinity\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: ProcessorAffinity\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.ProcessorAffinity\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ProcessorAffinity\n- uid: System.IntPtr\n  parent: System\n  isExternal: true\n  name: IntPtr\n  nameWithType: IntPtr\n  fullName: System.IntPtr\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ResetIdealProcessor\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: ResetIdealProcessor()\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.ResetIdealProcessor()\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ResetIdealProcessor()\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.StartAddress\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: StartAddress\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.StartAddress\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.StartAddress\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.StartTime\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: StartTime\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.StartTime\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.StartTime\n- uid: System.DateTime\n  parent: System\n  isExternal: true\n  name: DateTime\n  nameWithType: DateTime\n  fullName: System.DateTime\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: ThreadState\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.ThreadState\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ThreadState\n  parent: System.Diagnostics\n  isExternal: false\n  name: ThreadState\n  nameWithType: ThreadState\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ThreadState\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.TotalProcessorTime\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: TotalProcessorTime\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.TotalProcessorTime\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.TotalProcessorTime\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: UserProcessorTime\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: WaitReason\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.WaitReason\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ThreadWaitReason\n  parent: System.Diagnostics\n  isExternal: false\n  name: ThreadWaitReason\n  nameWithType: ThreadWaitReason\n  fullName: System.Diagnostics.ThreadWaitReason\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.BasePriority*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: BasePriority\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.BasePriority\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.CurrentPriority*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: CurrentPriority\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.CurrentPriority\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.Id*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: Id\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.Id\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.IdealProcessor*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: IdealProcessor\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.IdealProcessor\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityBoostEnabled*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: PriorityBoostEnabled\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.PriorityBoostEnabled\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PriorityLevel*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: PriorityLevel\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.PriorityLevel\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: PrivilegedProcessorTime\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.PrivilegedProcessorTime\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ProcessorAffinity*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: ProcessorAffinity\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.ProcessorAffinity\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ResetIdealProcessor*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: ResetIdealProcessor\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.ResetIdealProcessor\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.StartAddress*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: StartAddress\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.StartAddress\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.StartTime*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: StartTime\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.StartTime\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.ThreadState*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: ThreadState\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.ThreadState\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.TotalProcessorTime*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: TotalProcessorTime\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.TotalProcessorTime\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: UserProcessorTime\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.UserProcessorTime\n- uid: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread.WaitReason*\n  parent: System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread\n  isExternal: false\n  name: WaitReason\n  nameWithType: ProcessThread.WaitReason\n"}