{"nodes":[{"pos":[316,360],"content":"Represents the method to call as the client.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Represents the method to call as the client.","pos":[0,44]}]},{"pos":[372,689],"content":"Use this delegate to specify a method to call when impersonating the client. The connecting client's permissions are applied to the remote server. For example, if the connecting client tries to request the contents of a file on the server, the client can request only files that it has sufficient permissions to open.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Use this delegate to specify a method to call when impersonating the client. The connecting client's permissions are applied to the remote server. For example, if the connecting client tries to request the contents of a file on the server, the client can request only files that it has sufficient permissions to open.","pos":[0,317],"nodes":[{"content":"Use this delegate to specify a method to call when impersonating the client.","pos":[0,76]},{"content":"The connecting client's permissions are applied to the remote server.","pos":[77,146]},{"content":"For example, if the connecting client tries to request the contents of a file on the server, the client can request only files that it has sufficient permissions to open.","pos":[147,317]}]}]}],"content":"### YamlMime:ManagedReference\nitems:\n- uid: System.IO.Pipes.PipeStreamImpersonationWorker\n  id: PipeStreamImpersonationWorker\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: PipeStreamImpersonationWorker\n  nameWithType: PipeStreamImpersonationWorker\n  fullName: System.IO.Pipes.PipeStreamImpersonationWorker\n  type: Delegate\n  summary: Represents the method to call as the client.\n  remarks: Use this delegate to specify a method to call when impersonating the client. The connecting client's permissions are applied to the remote server. For example, if the connecting client tries to request the contents of a file on the server, the client can request only files that it has sufficient permissions to open.\n  syntax:\n    content: public delegate void PipeStreamImpersonationWorker();\n  inheritance:\n  - System.Delegate\n  platform:\n  - net462\nreferences:\n- uid: System.Delegate\n  isExternal: false\n  name: System.Delegate\n"}