{"nodes":[{"pos":[254,420],"content":"Represents the method that will handle the <bpt id=\"p1\">&lt;xref href=\"System.IO.FileSystemWatcher.Renamed\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p1\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> event of a <bpt id=\"p2\">&lt;xref href=\"System.IO.FileSystemWatcher\"&gt;</bpt><ept id=\"p2\">&lt;/xref&gt;</ept> class.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"source":"Represents the method that will handle the <xref href=\"System.IO.FileSystemWatcher.Renamed\"></xref> event of a <xref href=\"System.IO.FileSystemWatcher\"></xref> class."},{"pos":[432,817],"content":"When you create a RenamedEventHandler delegate, you identify the method that will handle the event. To associate the event with your event handler, add an instance of the delegate to the event. The event handler is called whenever the event occurs, unless you remove the delegate. For more information about event handler delegates, see [Events](~/add/includes/ajax-current-ext-md.md).","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"extradata":"MT","nodes":[{"content":"When you create a RenamedEventHandler delegate, you identify the method that will handle the event.","pos":[0,99]},{"content":"To associate the event with your event handler, add an instance of the delegate to the event.","pos":[100,193]},{"content":"The event handler is called whenever the event occurs, unless you remove the delegate.","pos":[194,280]},{"content":"For more information about event handler delegates, see <bpt id=\"p1\">[</bpt>Events<ept id=\"p1\">](~/add/includes/ajax-current-ext-md.md)</ept>.","pos":[281,385],"source":" For more information about event handler delegates, see [Events](~/add/includes/ajax-current-ext-md.md)."}]}],"content":"### YamlMime:ManagedReference\nitems:\n- uid: System.IO.RenamedEventHandler\n  id: RenamedEventHandler\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: RenamedEventHandler\n  nameWithType: RenamedEventHandler\n  fullName: System.IO.RenamedEventHandler\n  type: Delegate\n  summary: Represents the method that will handle the <xref href=\"System.IO.FileSystemWatcher.Renamed\"></xref> event of a <xref href=\"System.IO.FileSystemWatcher\"></xref> class.\n  remarks: When you create a RenamedEventHandler delegate, you identify the method that will handle the event. To associate the event with your event handler, add an instance of the delegate to the event. The event handler is called whenever the event occurs, unless you remove the delegate. For more information about event handler delegates, see [Events](~/add/includes/ajax-current-ext-md.md).\n  example:\n  - \"The following example shows how to create a FileSystemWatcher to monitor file changes (creates, deletes, renames, changes) occurring on a disk drive. The example also shows how to properly receive error notifications.  \\n  \\n [!code-cs[FileSystemWatcher#1](~/add/codesnippet/csharp/t-system.io.renamedevent_0_1.cs)]\\n [!code-vb[FileSystemWatcher#1](~/add/codesnippet/visualbasic/t-system.io.renamedevent_0_1.vb)]\"\n  syntax:\n    content: public delegate void RenamedEventHandler(object sender, RenamedEventArgs e);\n  inheritance:\n  - System.Delegate\n  platform:\n  - net462\nreferences:\n- uid: System.Delegate\n  isExternal: false\n  name: System.Delegate\n"}