{"nodes":[{"pos":[270,342],"content":"Defines a reference to a method that handles changes to monitored items.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"Defines a reference to a method that handles changes to monitored items.","pos":[0,72]}]},{"pos":[354,969],"content":"The OnChangedCallback delegate is used by a change monitor to signal to a cache implementation that a change has occurred in an object whose contents are cached. The task of any implementation of the <xref:System.Runtime.Caching.ChangeMonitor> type is to monitor for changes in objects that are cached. For example, if the contents of a file are contained in a cache entry, and if the file is updated, its related cache entry must be changed also. In a typical cache implementation, a derived <xref:System.Runtime.Caching.ChangeMonitor> instance uses a OnChangedCallback delegate to notify the cache about a change.","needQuote":true,"needEscape":true,"nodes":[{"content":"The OnChangedCallback delegate is used by a change monitor to signal to a cache implementation that a change has occurred in an object whose contents are cached. The task of any implementation of the <xref:System.Runtime.Caching.ChangeMonitor> type is to monitor for changes in objects that are cached. For example, if the contents of a file are contained in a cache entry, and if the file is updated, its related cache entry must be changed also. In a typical cache implementation, a derived <xref:System.Runtime.Caching.ChangeMonitor> instance uses a OnChangedCallback delegate to notify the cache about a change.","pos":[0,615],"nodes":[{"content":"The OnChangedCallback delegate is used by a change monitor to signal to a cache implementation that a change has occurred in an object whose contents are cached.","pos":[0,161]},{"content":"The task of any implementation of the &lt;xref:System.Runtime.Caching.ChangeMonitor&gt; type is to monitor for changes in objects that are cached.","pos":[162,302],"source":" The task of any implementation of the <xref:System.Runtime.Caching.ChangeMonitor> type is to monitor for changes in objects that are cached."},{"content":"For example, if the contents of a file are contained in a cache entry, and if the file is updated, its related cache entry must be changed also.","pos":[303,447]},{"content":"In a typical cache implementation, a derived &lt;xref:System.Runtime.Caching.ChangeMonitor&gt; instance uses a OnChangedCallback delegate to notify the cache about a change.","pos":[448,615],"source":" In a typical cache implementation, a derived <xref:System.Runtime.Caching.ChangeMonitor> instance uses a OnChangedCallback delegate to notify the cache about a change."}]}]}],"content":"### YamlMime:ManagedReference\nitems:\n- uid: System.Runtime.Caching.OnChangedCallback\n  id: OnChangedCallback\n  langs:\n  - csharp\n  name: OnChangedCallback\n  nameWithType: OnChangedCallback\n  fullName: System.Runtime.Caching.OnChangedCallback\n  type: Delegate\n  summary: Defines a reference to a method that handles changes to monitored items.\n  remarks: The OnChangedCallback delegate is used by a change monitor to signal to a cache implementation that a change has occurred in an object whose contents are cached. The task of any implementation of the <xref:System.Runtime.Caching.ChangeMonitor> type is to monitor for changes in objects that are cached. For example, if the contents of a file are contained in a cache entry, and if the file is updated, its related cache entry must be changed also. In a typical cache implementation, a derived <xref:System.Runtime.Caching.ChangeMonitor> instance uses a OnChangedCallback delegate to notify the cache about a change.\n  syntax:\n    content: public delegate void OnChangedCallback(object state);\n  inheritance:\n  - System.Delegate\n  platform:\n  - net462\nreferences:\n- uid: System.Delegate\n  isExternal: false\n  name: System.Delegate\n"}